<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<comment>/data/pun-netapp_rie_cpubuild_rbuild/rbuild/ars/ARS_9.1.00/201512160229/ars/src/unix/ars/server/common/serverj_components/common/target/classes/arcatalog_en.xml</comment>
<entry key="8749">Approaching physical stack limit.</entry>
<entry key="8748">Semaphore operation timed out.</entry>
<entry key="8747">Unable to access thread local storage.</entry>
<entry key="8746">Unable to allocate thread local storage.</entry>
<entry key="8745">Unable to create a queue to process RPC requests.</entry>
<entry key="8744">Unable to perform semaphore operation.</entry>
<entry key="8743">Unable to lock a mutex.</entry>
<entry key="8742">Unable to create a semaphore.</entry>
<entry key="8741">Unable to create a mutex.</entry>
<entry key="8740">Unable to create a server thread.</entry>
<entry key="9827">The server identifier has changed but the current "AR Server" license key will still be honored.</entry>
<entry key="9826">Warning, the total number of reserved pool licenses exceeds the total number of floating licenses</entry>
<entry key="9825">Can not reduce the requested limit below the current number of licenses used. Please delete some user licenses before reducing the license limit.</entry>
<entry key="9824">Unable to initialize license audit mutex.</entry>
<entry key="9823">Corrupted license audit file.</entry>
<entry key="9822">Error writing license audit file</entry>
<entry key="9821">Error reading license audit file</entry>
<entry key="9820">Error opening license audit file</entry>
<entry key="8739">Notify content name can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8738">Notify footer name can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8737">Notify header name can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8736">An arithmetic error was encountered in a decimal calculation</entry>
<entry key="8735">Bad decimal value</entry>
<entry key="8734">Invalid currency code string length</entry>
<entry key="8733">Unrecognized currency part tag</entry>
<entry key="8732">Client type must be a non-negative integer.</entry>
<entry key="8731">Changing the type in the field mapping structure is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="8730">Changing the field mapping is not allowed for join fields</entry>
<entry key="8729">Vendor forms not allowed in join forms</entry>
<entry key="8728">Invalid vendor form definition</entry>
<entry key="8727">Invalid external table name in a vendor field mapping definition.</entry>
<entry key="8726">Guide calling itself is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="8725">Continuation button title is empty or too long</entry>
<entry key="8724">Goto action tag must be a field or value.</entry>
<entry key="8723">Goto active link action label empty or too long.</entry>
<entry key="8722">Guide name missing</entry>
<entry key="8721">Call guide ID is empty.</entry>
<entry key="8720">Open dialog value is empty.</entry>
<entry key="4019">This form contains duplicate or empty field labels.  Those labels have been replaced by their field ids. (ARWARN 4019)</entry>
<entry key="4018">This file contains duplicate or empty field titles.  Those titles have been replaced by their field ids. (ARWARN 4018)</entry>
<entry key="4017">This file contains duplicate or empty field titles.  A number has been appended to those titles. (ARWARN 4017)</entry>
<entry key="4016">You made but did not save changes to the Save Mapping window. If you continue, your changes will be lost. (ARWARN 4016)</entry>
<entry key="4015">You have not saved your changes to the current fallback mappings.\nIf you continue, your changes will not be used for this import. (ARWARN 4015)</entry>
<entry key="4014">Copy unprocessed import records to the log file? (ARWARN 4014)</entry>
<entry key="4013">Did not find any matching fields to add as new mappings (ARWARN 4013)</entry>
<entry key="4012">Exit Import Tool?</entry>
<entry key="4011">Duplicate name for mapping.\nDo you want to overwrite the existing mapping? (ARWARN 4011)</entry>
<entry key="4010">Mapping "{0}" not loaded (ARWARN 4010)</entry>
<entry key="9804">A required form for Email is missing.  Server will attempt to import the form in place. Please verify the form gets imported or import it manually to ensure the Email Engine will work properly.</entry>
<entry key="9803">Cannot locate mailbox.</entry>
<entry key="9802">Email attachment mapping is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="9801">Couldn't locate the Email form.</entry>
<entry key="9800">The reserved fields already exist on this email form.</entry>
<entry key="8719">Guide Mode is not within a valid range. Setting it to zero</entry>
<entry key="8718">The signal {0} is not valid and is ignored</entry>
<entry key="8717">The value for the Application check interval is not within the legal range of 0 to 3600 seconds</entry>
<entry key="8716">The RPC socket number for the Approval Server process is not one of the legal values (390600, 390621 - 390634, 390636 - 390669, 390680 - 390694)</entry>
<entry key="8715">Bad automation string in the OLE Automation active link action.</entry>
<entry key="8714">Bad OLE Automation active link action Parameter.</entry>
<entry key="8713">Empty OLE Automation active link action Parameter.</entry>
<entry key="8712">Empty OLE Automation active link action Parameter List.</entry>
<entry key="8711">Empty OLE Automation active link action Method.</entry>
<entry key="8710">Bad OLE Automation active link action Method name.</entry>
<entry key="4009">Are you sure you want to start importing?</entry>
<entry key="4008">Record {0} : Field "{1}" truncated to {2} characters (ARWARN 4008)</entry>
<entry key="4007">Are you sure you want to delete all mappings?</entry>
<entry key="4006">You have not saved your changes to the current mapping --\nif you continue, those changes will not be used for this import (ARWARN 4006)</entry>
<entry key="4005">You have not added or saved your changes to the current mapping --\nif you continue, those changes will be lost (ARWARN 4005)</entry>
<entry key="4004">You have not saved or imported data with the current mappings --\nif you continue, the mappings will be lost (ARWARN 4004)</entry>
<entry key="4003">You have not saved or imported data with the current mappings --\n if you continue, the mappings will be lost. (ARWARN 4003)</entry>
<entry key="4002">The specified import file has only one field --\nensure that you specified the import file correctly. (ARWARN 4002)</entry>
<entry key="4001">Import of {0} started (ARNOTE 4001)</entry>
<entry key="4000">Import completed successfully -- {0} records imported (ARNOTE 4000)</entry>
<entry key="8709">Bad OLE Automation active link action Method.</entry>
<entry key="8708">Bad OLE class ID or method ID, or interface of an OLE automation active link.</entry>
<entry key="8707">Bad OLE server or parameter name.</entry>
<entry key="8706">Bad ARCOMValueStruct variable value.</entry>
<entry key="8705">OLE Automation active link action method list can not be empty.</entry>
<entry key="8704">OLE Automation active link action can not be empty.</entry>
<entry key="8703">Bad attachment size</entry>
<entry key="8702">Bad attachment locator buffer pointer</entry>
<entry key="8701">Bad attachment locator buffer size</entry>
<entry key="8700">Attachment locator types can only be filename or the buffer. Use only these types.</entry>
<entry key="199">Missing name for a macro parameter in the active link action.</entry>
<entry key="198">Cannot use the $DEFAULT$ keyword as a default value or in a qualification</entry>
<entry key="197">Unrecognized keyword</entry>
<entry key="196">Macro branch of active link action must include both a name and macro text</entry>
<entry key="195">Filter/active Link/escalation 'set field' definition is missing</entry>
<entry key="194">The ARAssignFieldStruct tag for filter/active link/escalation is not recognized.</entry>
<entry key="193">One or more fields, or assignment items in the field or assignment list, encountered an error.</entry>
<entry key="192">Field/assignment list item is empty</entry>
<entry key="191">Unrecognized assign type</entry>
<entry key="190">Unrecognized active link action type</entry>
<entry key="189">Active link does not have an action defined</entry>
<entry key="188">On Return or On Menu choice condition does not have a Field specified.</entry>
<entry key="187">Execute mask parameter is out of bounds</entry>
<entry key="186">Cannot assign character menu to system core or reserved fields.</entry>
<entry key="185">Cannot assign default value to system core or reserved fields (except Entry ID).</entry>
<entry key="184">Quotation mark can not be used in Entry ID field.</entry>
<entry key="183">Duplicate group ID was specified in permission list</entry>
<entry key="182">Too many actions have been specified for this filter/active link/escalation</entry>
<entry key="181">The ID specified for this field is in the reserved field range</entry>
<entry key="180">Specified length for a character type is longer than the maximum allowed length.</entry>
<entry key="2141">The following field names/ids have blank labels in your form</entry>
<entry key="2140">Other forms depend on current form . Deleting this form will cause\n forms that depend on it to be deleted. Are you sure you want to Continue?</entry>
<entry key="3227">For 'Alert API' plugins, Client Port, Client IP Address and Server IP Address cannot be NULL. For other plugins, Plugin Name and Plugin Values cannot be NULL.</entry>
<entry key="179">Pattern in a character limit is invalid</entry>
<entry key="3226">User with this registration type and required values is already registered.</entry>
<entry key="178">Field ID can not be empty, please provide an field id or enter 0 for the system to assign a value.</entry>
<entry key="3225">Form does not allow non-admin to delete.</entry>
<entry key="177">Change permission can not be given to a view-only group.</entry>
<entry key="176">Duplicate name in the selection list.</entry>
<entry key="175">The Number of Rows value of the display parameter is out of range.</entry>
<entry key="174">Display type specified is incompatible for the data type.</entry>
<entry key="173">Language specified in the control record not recognized -- using default on server</entry>
<entry key="172">The required service is not available.</entry>
<entry key="171">The specified status field value is out of range.</entry>
<entry key="2139">Changes in Current view will be Saved -- if You Continue!</entry>
<entry key="170">Status history tag is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="2138">You are attempting to delete a Distributed Server form or field.\nDo you wish to continue?</entry>
<entry key="2137">Changes on the mapping fields screen will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="2136">The selected pending mappings will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2135">The selected distributed mapping will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2134">You must be a member of the Administrator or Subadministrator group with a fixed license to use this tool</entry>
<entry key="2133">Full text index operations will be shut down</entry>
<entry key="2132">Full text index operations will be started</entry>
<entry key="2131">Incompatible data types in qualification line</entry>
<entry key="2130">You are logged in as a subadministrator --\naccess to some structures and functions has been disabled</entry>
<entry key="169">Execution order value is out of range</entry>
<entry key="168">One of the field/assignments in the set filter/active link/escalation definition is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="167">The limit specified for the field does not match the field's data type.</entry>
<entry key="166">The data type specified does not match the field's data type.</entry>
<entry key="165">The numItems value for a parameter was not set.</entry>
<entry key="163">The tag for the notify fields is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="162">Notify Text is empty or too long</entry>
<entry key="161">The session identifier in the control record is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="2129">Your escalation definition and all associated actions will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="160">Data Decompression has failed.</entry>
<entry key="2128">Your escalation action will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2127">This operation (FTS Re-index) could take a long time</entry>
<entry key="2126">You currently have an escalation time specified</entry>
<entry key="2125">Exit Administrator Tool?</entry>
<entry key="2124">Your form view name is not unique</entry>
<entry key="2123">Your form view will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2122">Your active link action will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2121">Your filter action will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2120">Additional errors were truncated</entry>
<entry key="4654">The Process field is required on Detail form but is missing.</entry>
<entry key="4653">The Next Approver field is required on Sig Line form but is missing.</entry>
<entry key="4652">The Entry ID field is required on Detail form but is missing.</entry>
<entry key="4651">The Form field is required on Detail form but is missing.</entry>
<entry key="4650">The Completion field is required on Detail form but is missing.</entry>
<entry key="159">A server name is not supplied.</entry>
<entry key="158">Entry ID field can not exceed 10 characters.</entry>
<entry key="157">Field IDs below 100 are reserved for core fields</entry>
<entry key="156">The buffer for holding the input value is not specified.</entry>
<entry key="3203">Error parsing field pairs from dynamic permission inheritance property.</entry>
<entry key="155">The buffer for holding the return value is not specified.</entry>
<entry key="3202">Field defined in dynamic permission inheritance property not found.</entry>
<entry key="154">The system encountered an error during a call to allocate memory space.</entry>
<entry key="3201">Object does not have a dynamic permission inheritance property.</entry>
<entry key="153">The specified sort method is invalid on one of the entries in the sort list.</entry>
<entry key="3200">Invalid dynamic permission inheritance object property format.</entry>
<entry key="152">The value specified for the sort list parameter is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="151">Required form parameter is missing</entry>
<entry key="2119">The following fields (including data) and/or active links will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="150">A server name must be supplied in the control record</entry>
<entry key="2118">Administration operations require you to use the default socket 390600 --\nenvironment variable has been reset to the default socket</entry>
<entry key="2117">Your menu definition will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2115">Changes on the following screens will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="2114">The following field labels are duplicated in your form</entry>
<entry key="2113">The following fields (including data) will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2112">Language defined by LANG environment variable not recognized --\nusing default on server</entry>
<entry key="2111">Cannot load colormap with either user colors or default colors</entry>
<entry key="2110">Cannot load colormap with user colors -- default colors used</entry>
<entry key="149">A user name must be supplied in the control record</entry>
<entry key="148">The tag for the type of the field, value, or arithmetic operation is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="147">The value portion of a field, value, or arithmetic operation is empty.</entry>
<entry key="146">The tag specified for the arithmetic operation is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="145">The value portion of an arithmetic operator qualification structure is NULL.</entry>
<entry key="144">The tag for the relational operation is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="143">The value portion of a relational operator qualification structure is NULL.</entry>
<entry key="142">The tag for one of the nodes in the qualify condition structure is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="141">The Qualify None option can only be used at the top level of a qualification.</entry>
<entry key="2109">Your active link definition and all associated actions will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="140">The Status field must have a default value.</entry>
<entry key="2108">New text too long -- truncating to fit</entry>
<entry key="2107">Your form definition and all associated data will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2106">NO LICENSE</entry>
<entry key="2105">Your administrator command definition will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2104">You have not saved changes on this screen --\nthey will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="2103">Incorrect parameter specification -- check field name spelling</entry>
<entry key="2102">No structures are in the import file</entry>
<entry key="2101">Your filter definition and all associated actions will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="2100">You have specified a field ID within the reserved range</entry>
<entry key="1016">The server name in a parameter is longer than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="1015">The -x option requires a server name</entry>
<entry key="1014">A directory can be specified only if you specify a macro</entry>
<entry key="1013">The directory name in a parameter is longer than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="1012">The -d option requires a directory name</entry>
<entry key="1011">Two directories for startup macros have been specified</entry>
<entry key="1010">No servers are defined for the AR system in the directory file</entry>
<entry key="139">Option cannot be changed for core or reserved field with a fixed options definition.</entry>
<entry key="138">Filter/active link/escalation message number must be greater than 10000</entry>
<entry key="137">Invalid message type.</entry>
<entry key="499">Field is not allowed to participate in Association.</entry>
<entry key="136">The code specified for the notify mechanism in one of the filter actions is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="498">Association is not allowed on join or archive forms.</entry>
<entry key="135">One of the filter action codes was not recognized.</entry>
<entry key="497">Association enforcement can not be null.</entry>
<entry key="134">One of the items specified in the list is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="496">Cardinality of an association can not be null.</entry>
<entry key="133">The list parameter is an invalid list.</entry>
<entry key="495">Tag Name can not be empty.</entry>
<entry key="132">The list parameter is an empty list.</entry>
<entry key="494">Primary Key Foreign Key mapping can not be empty.</entry>
<entry key="131">One of the character menu type tags is not recognized.</entry>
<entry key="493">Association does not exist on server.</entry>
<entry key="130">One of the entries in the character menu is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="492">Duplicate association name.</entry>
<entry key="491">You do not have access to the specified association.</entry>
<entry key="490">Invalid preference server option, out of range.</entry>
<entry key="1009">Two startup macros have been specified</entry>
<entry key="1008">The macro name in a parameter is longer than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="1007">Cannot connect to the X server</entry>
<entry key="1006">Cannot read the configuration file --\nARHOME environment variable may be set incorrectly</entry>
<entry key="1005">Parameters can be specified only if you specify a macro</entry>
<entry key="1004">Unrecognized command line option</entry>
<entry key="1003">The format for the -p option is  -p name = value</entry>
<entry key="1002">The -p option requires a substitution parameter and a value</entry>
<entry key="1001">The -e and -i options require a macro name</entry>
<entry key="1000">Cannot allocate memory on startup</entry>
<entry key="4620">No Approval Preview Signature Line form was found</entry>
<entry key="129">Field limit definition is invalid</entry>
<entry key="128">One of the permission tags is not recognized.</entry>
<entry key="127">One of the items in the permission list is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="489">At least one set field failed in a multi-field operation</entry>
<entry key="126">One of the statistical operation codes is not recognized.</entry>
<entry key="488">Field creation error occurred at the indicated list position.</entry>
<entry key="125">One of the entries specified in the statistics operation list is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="487">Set field status list cannot be empty.</entry>
<entry key="124">One of the items specified in the field or value list contains error.</entry>
<entry key="486">The list parameter does not have the same item count as in the Field ID list.</entry>
<entry key="123">Unrecognized server information tag</entry>
<entry key="485">The reservedIdOKList parameter in the ARCreateMultipleFields() API function is blank. This parameter must be either "Yes" or "No" or "1" or "0".</entry>
<entry key="122">The value for the list of information to retrieve from the server is empty.</entry>
<entry key="121">Invalid entry in the entry id list.</entry>
<entry key="483">Please restart the AR System Server for the changes to take effect</entry>
<entry key="120">Unsupported datatype in this client</entry>
<entry key="482">This View Form contains empty Request IDs. Ensure that the key field is set to an unique non-blank field to avoid data corruption.</entry>
<entry key="481">Requested database table not found.  Please check the spelling (table name is case-sensitive)</entry>
<entry key="480">Status History field is not supported on View forms</entry>
<entry key="2447">Distributed Fields cannot be added to a Join Form.\nSelect a Regular Form.</entry>
<entry key="2446">There are no Toolbar Items on any of the Menu Items</entry>
<entry key="2445">&lt;non-matching data types&gt;</entry>
<entry key="4619">Duplicate Approval Preview signature Line forms found, Only one is allowed.</entry>
<entry key="4618">Duplicate Approval Forms found, Only one is allowed.</entry>
<entry key="4617">Duplicate Approval Notification forms found, Only one is allowed.</entry>
<entry key="4616">Duplicate Approval Administration forms found. Only one is allowed.</entry>
<entry key="4615">A join form of the Detail-Signature form can not be found.</entry>
<entry key="4614">Field names are part of the string that has been set in Send to Other, Subject, and Message fields in the AP:Notification entry. These field names could not be resolved into field IDs.</entry>
<entry key="4613">The issued Update-config command did not have a tag for the config parameter.</entry>
<entry key="4612">No join is defined between the approval detail and signature line forms</entry>
<entry key="4611">No join is defined between the form and the approval detail form</entry>
<entry key="4610">No process is associated with this form.</entry>
<entry key="119">Unrecognized create mode</entry>
<entry key="118">Unrecognized or inappropriate value for field option</entry>
<entry key="117">Command string is empty or longer than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="479">The temporary column control.unicode63handled, created for upgrading the 6.3 Unicode database to a 7.0 database, could not be deleted.  Please delete this column manually.</entry>
<entry key="116">Filter does not have an action defined</entry>
<entry key="478">This 6.3 Unicode database is not yet ready for upgrade. Please contact Customer Service for details on how to prepare your database before attempting an upgrade to a 7.0 Unicode database.</entry>
<entry key="115">Operation mask parameter is out of bounds</entry>
<entry key="477">Oracle 8.0 is no longer supported by upgrade</entry>
<entry key="114">One or more values in the names list is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="476">Too many arguments specified for upgrade program</entry>
<entry key="113">Name list parameter is empty</entry>
<entry key="475">Too few arguments specified for upgrade program</entry>
<entry key="112">One or more values in the names list is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="474">No licenses in supplied file.</entry>
<entry key="111">Incorrect data type value for this data type field.</entry>
<entry key="110">Incorrect data type value for this parameter.</entry>
<entry key="470">User Cache utilities are disabled.</entry>
<entry key="4609">The specified process can not be found.</entry>
<entry key="4608">MoreInfo-xxx command can only be issued from the More Information form.</entry>
<entry key="4607">Process allows only one 'next approver' but two or more were specified</entry>
<entry key="4606">Multiple approval process are associated with this application, but none is specified for this new approval process to use.</entry>
<entry key="4605">Sig-xxx command requires process to match details if process is specified</entry>
<entry key="4604">Sig-xxx command requires form to be the approval signature line form</entry>
<entry key="4603">Field specified for first approver is not defined on the form</entry>
<entry key="4602">AR System server does not support Remedy Application Service user</entry>
<entry key="4601">Multiple Next Approvers found but the current setting only allows one.</entry>
<entry key="4600">The approval process for the indicated entry ID is already in progress. New approval detail entry can not be created.</entry>
<entry key="109">Filename is longer than maximum allowed filename</entry>
<entry key="108">Field display definition is incorrect</entry>
<entry key="107">Type of statistical operation is not specified.</entry>
<entry key="469">Warning, this key is not valid for this server.</entry>
<entry key="106">No entry is specified for this statistical operation.</entry>
<entry key="468">Error reading license cache table.</entry>
<entry key="105">NULL pointer for result list</entry>
<entry key="467">AR Server license import option can only be 0 or 1.</entry>
<entry key="104">Required Field/Value list item is empty.</entry>
<entry key="466">Invalid or pre 6.0 AR Server license file.</entry>
<entry key="103">The length of the name parameter (or name field in a parameter) is longer than the maximum allowed length.</entry>
<entry key="465">Cannot change the form mapping criteria in a Lite licensed AR Server.</entry>
<entry key="102">Required name parameter (or name field in a parameter) is empty.</entry>
<entry key="464">Cannot change the form name in a Lite licensed AR Server.</entry>
<entry key="101">Entry ID parameter length is longer than the maximum allowed length.</entry>
<entry key="463">Cannot create a form in a Lite licensed AR Server.</entry>
<entry key="100">Required Entry ID is empty.</entry>
<entry key="462">The form is not a member of a Lite licensed application.</entry>
<entry key="461">The AR Server version does not match the Lite license AR Server version included with the licensed application.</entry>
<entry key="460">Audit Configuration information cannot be found in the ar.conf/ar.cfg file.</entry>
<entry key="9150">Error while opening the armonitor lock file.</entry>
<entry key="453">The tag has an invalid format.</entry>
<entry key="452">Could not find or read the optional license tags file.</entry>
<entry key="451">Report definition file failed to load into server. The operation will continue without this file.</entry>
<entry key="450">Cannot find the report definition file.\nThe operation will continue without the file identified.</entry>
<entry key="9145">Upgrade of system form failed because the definition file is missing an expected field</entry>
<entry key="9144">Upgrade of system form failed because the definition file is not the required version</entry>
<entry key="9143">Conversion of a datetime string to timestamp failed</entry>
<entry key="9142">Conversion of time value to a string failed</entry>
<entry key="9141">Conversion of timestamp to a string failed</entry>
<entry key="448">File size limit exceeded</entry>
<entry key="447">Server information associated with this tag has an invalid value.</entry>
<entry key="446">Changing the field option of the field is not allowed </entry>
<entry key="445">Could not resolve the JNI method </entry>
<entry key="444">Could not resolve the JNI class</entry>
<entry key="442">The required API input argument is empty.</entry>
<entry key="441">Invalid array index, out of range</entry>
<entry key="9135">Invalid URL</entry>
<entry key="9134">Invalid number of arguments</entry>
<entry key="9133">Web Service Registry Location cannot be empty</entry>
<entry key="9132">The output default value of element does not match the input value.</entry>
<entry key="9131">XML Output mapping cannot be Empty.</entry>
<entry key="9130">Error encountered while executing a Web Service</entry>
<entry key="439">Error changing field column length; ensure no existing data in the field exceeds the requested length before retrying</entry>
<entry key="438">Cache reload failure.</entry>
<entry key="437">The form data definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="436">Invalid format for server information setting, please check server name, port, etc.</entry>
<entry key="8044">Reload of logging config file failed.</entry>
<entry key="435">Administrative operations must be enabled before you can modify this server setting.</entry>
<entry key="8043">Unexpected use of query parameter</entry>
<entry key="434">An invalid or a corrupt lock block definition was skipped</entry>
<entry key="8042">Request to not enforce associations was ignored because user is not an administrator</entry>
<entry key="433">Not a lock block definition</entry>
<entry key="8041">Could not load the server API description file</entry>
<entry key="432">Currency field has too many functional currencies to allow indexing</entry>
<entry key="8040">Could not load the server configuration file</entry>
<entry key="431">Field of this type cannot be included in a multi-column index.</entry>
<entry key="430">Field ID exceeds the maximum allowed value.</entry>
<entry key="1301">No such form -- make a selection from the list</entry>
<entry key="1300">Error while processing selected entries.  Continue processing, suppressing further errors or cancel the operation.</entry>
<entry key="8039">Oracle database is using an unsupported NLS_LENGTH_SEMANTICS value</entry>
<entry key="8038">Request to not fire filter workflow on merge was ignored because user is not an administrator</entry>
<entry key="429">The VUI definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="8037">Index length longer than 255 bytes may not work on all databases.</entry>
<entry key="8036">The system can not recognize some characters. Unrecognized characters are ignored.</entry>
<entry key="8035">Referenced character menu can not be found.</entry>
<entry key="8034">Full Text floating license timeout change will only take effect after server restart.</entry>
<entry key="8033">Floating License Timeout change will only take effect after server restart.</entry>
<entry key="424">Push fields actions that affect entries in other forms can only affect forms on the same server in a filter/escalation</entry>
<entry key="8032">An owned container cannot have a list of subadministrator groups. The list is disregarded.</entry>
<entry key="423">The container definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="8031">Some of the fields and/or workflow in this form are not supported in this version of the client</entry>
<entry key="422">Unrecognized escalation action type</entry>
<entry key="421">Incomplete field mapping definition</entry>
<entry key="420">Invalid field type</entry>
<entry key="9110">Server does not have a valid host id.  Please correct this error to enable licensing for this server</entry>
<entry key="8029">One or more entries matched filter conditions --\n your current setting considered any match as an error.</entry>
<entry key="419">Incomplete view form definition</entry>
<entry key="418">Incomplete join form definition</entry>
<entry key="417">The group name is not a defined group.</entry>
<entry key="416">The distributed mapping definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="415">The escalation definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="414">The character menu definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="413">The Active link definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="412">The import file is in an incorrect format</entry>
<entry key="411">The command definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="410">The filter definition can not be found in the specified file.</entry>
<entry key="8380">The operation failed because another user has reserved the association</entry>
<entry key="9103">DSO is not licensed.</entry>
<entry key="9102">Invalid Run Process or Direct SQL command.</entry>
<entry key="9101">The direct SQL and run process commands are valid only as server-side processes, not as client-side.</entry>
<entry key="9100">The command does not occur on the local server</entry>
<entry key="409">No definition is in the file</entry>
<entry key="408">Selection data type requires a selection definition.</entry>
<entry key="8379">The operation failed because another user has reserved the data file.</entry>
<entry key="407">Duplicate field/VUI ID in the form definition.</entry>
<entry key="8378">The Server Version Control Reservation Label fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="406">One of the core fields is missing from the form file definition</entry>
<entry key="8377">AR Server failed to auto reserve an object.</entry>
<entry key="405">A core definition from the definition file is incorrect</entry>
<entry key="8376">AR Server auto reserved an object.</entry>
<entry key="404">Field ID is in the core field range but is not defined core field.</entry>
<entry key="8375">The Server Version Control Ext Reservation fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="403">The form definition file field/VUI count does not the match number of fields/VUIs in the file</entry>
<entry key="8374">The Server Version Control Reservation Repository type can only be 0 for ARS or 10 for External type.</entry>
<entry key="8011">Violation of FOREIGN KEY constraint.</entry>
<entry key="402">Incorrect format in the definition file</entry>
<entry key="8373">The operation failed because the related application object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8010">Violation of PRIMARY KEY constraint.</entry>
<entry key="401">Form definition in the source file is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="8372">The operation failed because the related container object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="400">The file specified for a form does not hold a form definition</entry>
<entry key="8371">The operation failed because the related escalation object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8370">The operation failed because the related active link object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8369">The operation failed because the related filter object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8368">The operation failed because the dependent join form object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8005">The context for the called filter is missing.</entry>
<entry key="8367">The operation failed because the image object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8004">An error handler can not use itself as its own error handler.</entry>
<entry key="8366">The operation failed because the application object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8003">Could not locate error handler in schema workflow list</entry>
<entry key="8365">The operation failed because the container object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8002">Filter error handlers exceeded the maximum number of levels.</entry>
<entry key="8364">The operation failed because the escalation object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8001">The error handler name can not exceed 254 characters.</entry>
<entry key="8363">The operation failed because the character menu object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8000">The error handler can not be found on this server.</entry>
<entry key="8362">The operation failed because the active link object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="8361">The operation failed because the filter object is already reserved </entry>
<entry key="8360">The operation failed because the form object is already reserved</entry>
<entry key="1628">A filename is required when generating a report to an external report writer</entry>
<entry key="1627">The type of external report specified is not recognized</entry>
<entry key="1626">Cannot generate a report to file or to application when using an external report writer</entry>
<entry key="1625">Reporting to an external report writer is supported on the Windows platform only</entry>
<entry key="1624">A problem was encountered accessing the active link debug file</entry>
<entry key="1623">Unable to Export View</entry>
<entry key="1622">An error occurred while updating the server.--\nView has not been saved.</entry>
<entry key="8359">The operation succeeded, but all or some of the corresponding labeled object entries were not added to the AR System Version Control: Labeled Object form</entry>
<entry key="8358">The operation succeeded, but label was not created to the AR System Version Control: Label form</entry>
<entry key="8357">The Server Version Control Labeled Object fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="8356">The Server Version Control Label fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="8355">The Defintion Files option on the Version control tab must be either 0 for save and 10 for not save.</entry>
<entry key="8354">The operation succeeded, but all or some of the corresponding log entries were not added to the AR System Version Control: Object Modification Log form</entry>
<entry key="8353">The Server Version Control Object Modification Log fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="8352">The Server Version Control Task fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="8351">Version control object modification log mode must be either 0 for disabled mode or 10 for enabled mode.</entry>
<entry key="1611">Multiple entries match active link conditions --\nthis operation has been defined so that multiple matches generate an error</entry>
<entry key="1610">You must set the environment variable ARHELP to point to the help directory.\n This is usually the directory named help under the AR System install directory</entry>
<entry key="1609">The statistic operation is too complex --\nit references over 50 distinct fields</entry>
<entry key="1608">Value exceeded report maximum length</entry>
<entry key="1607">No admininistrator commands are defined</entry>
<entry key="1606">No user commands are defined</entry>
<entry key="1605">Active link trying to set non-existent field.</entry>
<entry key="1604">Active link trying to set non-existent menu. Resetting to the default menu</entry>
<entry key="1603">Set fields active link running a process failed</entry>
<entry key="1602">No item matches active link conditions and this operation has been defined so that no match generates an error</entry>
<entry key="1601">Overflow while expanding active link macro parameter (maximum expanded parameter is 4096 bytes)</entry>
<entry key="9782">Invalid role format: {0}</entry>
<entry key="1600">Overflow while expanding active link process (maximum expanded command is 4096 bytes)</entry>
<entry key="9781">Role name was not found.  Verify that the role name is valid</entry>
<entry key="9761">Unrecognized internal workflow API function</entry>
<entry key="9760">Workflow API function called from improper filter phase</entry>
<entry key="8318">The object cannot be reserved because it does not exist on the server. You must save an object on the server before you can reserve it.</entry>
<entry key="8317">The operation failed because another user has reserved the related application</entry>
<entry key="8316">The operation failed because another user has reserved the related container</entry>
<entry key="8315">The operation failed because another user has reserved the related escalation</entry>
<entry key="8314">The operation failed because another user has reserved the related active link</entry>
<entry key="8313">The operation failed because another user has reserved the related filter</entry>
<entry key="8312">The operation failed because another user has reserved the dependent join form</entry>
<entry key="8311">The operation failed because another user has reserved the image</entry>
<entry key="8310">The operation failed because another user has reserved the application</entry>
<entry key="9759">Extension library called with no filter context</entry>
<entry key="9758">Invalid filter processing call made outside of filter context</entry>
<entry key="9757">Invalid call made from within filter context</entry>
<entry key="9755">Error encountered while initializing (Initialization routine) the shared library</entry>
<entry key="9754">The shared library has an invalid RPC program number.</entry>
<entry key="9753">The shared library is not loaded because it violates one of the prerequisites.</entry>
<entry key="9752">The shared library does not provide an Identification routine implementation</entry>
<entry key="9751">The shared library identification is invalid or duplicate</entry>
<entry key="9750">Error encountered while loading the shared library</entry>
<entry key="8309">The operation failed because another user has reserved the container</entry>
<entry key="8308">The operation failed because another user has reserved the escalation</entry>
<entry key="8307">The operation failed because another user has reserved the character menu</entry>
<entry key="8306">The operation failed because another user has reserved the active link</entry>
<entry key="8305">The operation failed because another user has reserved the filter</entry>
<entry key="8304">The operation failed because another user has reserved the form</entry>
<entry key="8303">The requested object is reserved by another user.</entry>
<entry key="8302">The data entered is invalid. The Server Version Control Reservation mode can only be 0 for disabled mode or 10 for enabled mode.</entry>
<entry key="8301">The Server Version Control Reservation fields can only exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="9736">Merge Entry ID mismatch. Merge option was to return error on ID mismatch.</entry>
<entry key="9735">Invalid full text scan information in form object properties</entry>
<entry key="9730">The updating of metadata through the Metadata view forms is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="9722">The cleanup of object relationships was skipped for this server group member because this server is not top ranked for the Administration operation</entry>
<entry key="9721">The generation of object relationships was skipped for this server group member because this server is not top ranked for the Administration operation</entry>
<entry key="9720">The updating of object relationship data through the AR System Object Relationships form is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="8999">The Archive or Audit form is invalid. Archive or Audit form should be of proper type, proper permissions as the source form. \nPlease check the manual for requirements for a valid Archive or Audit form.</entry>
<entry key="8998">Cannot modify or create entries in an Archive or Audit form.</entry>
<entry key="8997">Turn off the archive or audit to this form in order to delete this form.</entry>
<entry key="8996">Archive not possible on Dialog forms,Archive forms,Vendor forms and Join forms.</entry>
<entry key="8995">Archive Type does not match the remaining archive information passed in.</entry>
<entry key="8994">Both the Source form and the Archive or Audit form must belong to the same Application.</entry>
<entry key="8993">If any of the Copy options are chosen, form name must be present.</entry>
<entry key="8992">An archive or audit form cannot be created for a source form because of a lack of memory or a database error. Archive/Audit for this form has been disabled.</entry>
<entry key="8991">Could not create this field in Archive or Audit Form. If this is a main form, then a field \nwith that ID exists in the Archive/Audit form and archive or audit will be disabled. If this is an \nArchive/Audit form then fields of this type cannot be created.</entry>
<entry key="8990">Cannot modify Limit Info or Permission for a data field in an Archive or Audit form. These values will be made NULL before setting.</entry>
<entry key="9719">Multiple entries match qualification criteria --\nthis operation has been defined so that multiple matches generate an error.</entry>
<entry key="9718">Unable to complete the full text index operation.</entry>
<entry key="3199">Unrecognized command line argument.</entry>
<entry key="3198">A value is missing for one of the arguments for the command line option.</entry>
<entry key="3197">Must specify the -x {server} option</entry>
<entry key="9713">The attempted bulk entry transaction failed due to an error in one of the individual operations.</entry>
<entry key="3196">Must specify the -s {form} option</entry>
<entry key="9712">Invalid action type for end of bulk entry transaction</entry>
<entry key="3195">Must specify the -e {entryID} option</entry>
<entry key="9711">No bulk entry transaction is in progress</entry>
<entry key="3194">Illegal value specified for -m option --\nlegal values are 0 (not master) and 1 (master)</entry>
<entry key="9710">Bulk entry transaction already in progress</entry>
<entry key="8989">Cannot delete data fields from Archive or Audit form.</entry>
<entry key="8988">Archive or Audit information could not be set for this form.</entry>
<entry key="8987">Change field action can only be: 1 to indicate a field or 0 to indicate a value.</entry>
<entry key="8986">The alias for this object is not unique. It will be set to empty string.</entry>
<entry key="8985">Roles permissions have been removed from the object because the object is not in a deployable application</entry>
<entry key="8984">Group permissions have been removed from the object because the object is in a deployable application</entry>
<entry key="8983">Changing the data type of the field is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="8982">Object is already owned by another application</entry>
<entry key="8981">Setting application owner is disallowed</entry>
<entry key="8980">Failed to open a system form definition file:</entry>
<entry key="9701">The Currency form does not contain the correct number of required currency fields.</entry>
<entry key="8979">The mailbox name information of the email notification message can not exceed 255 bytes</entry>
<entry key="8978">The organization list of the email notification message can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8977">The BCC list of the email notification message can not exceed 255 bytes</entry>
<entry key="8976">The CC list of the email notification message can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8975">The "reply to" information of the email notification message can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8974">The "from information" of email notification message can not exceed 255 bytes.</entry>
<entry key="8973">The reserved centralized file preference field can only exist on one form -- delete the duplicate</entry>
<entry key="8610">Please ensure correct overlay specific group(s) for the user.</entry>
<entry key="8972">The reserved centralized administrator preference field can only exist on one form -- delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="8971">The reserved centralized user preference field can only exist on one form -- delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="8970">The key for this entry must be unique in the XML input document.</entry>
<entry key="8609">Data Replication Status field value can not be updated</entry>
<entry key="8608">Error during data replication activity.</entry>
<entry key="8607">Entry operation not valid for this tenant.</entry>
<entry key="8969">A required attribute is missing from the XML input document.</entry>
<entry key="8606">Access denied to the specified tenant.</entry>
<entry key="8968">Invalid process definition.</entry>
<entry key="8605">Specified tenant is invalid</entry>
<entry key="8967">Required XML attribute is missing from the XML mapping</entry>
<entry key="8604">Parent ovelay group must be 0</entry>
<entry key="8966">Required XML element is missing from the XML mapping</entry>
<entry key="8603">Overlay Group ID field value can not be updated</entry>
<entry key="8965">The default notification mailbox is not specified</entry>
<entry key="8602">Tenant ID field value can not be updated</entry>
<entry key="8964">The number of entries is less than XML element's minOccurs value</entry>
<entry key="8601">Only SAAS Administrator can do operations on this object</entry>
<entry key="8963">The number of entries exceeds the XML element's maxOccurs value</entry>
<entry key="8600">Deletion of tenant is not allowed.</entry>
<entry key="8962">Unexpected element encountered in the input XML document</entry>
<entry key="8961">A required element is missing from the XML input document.</entry>
<entry key="8960">Server information data is in an incorrect format</entry>
<entry key="8959">The XML data type being converted is not supported by AR System.</entry>
<entry key="8958">The date value is invalid</entry>
<entry key="8957">The date format is invalid</entry>
<entry key="8956">This operation does not support the specified date part</entry>
<entry key="8955">XML import and export is not supported</entry>
<entry key="8954">A failure occurred while trying to open the file</entry>
<entry key="8953">Unable to load the arxmlutil library</entry>
<entry key="8952">An invalid XML document type was specified.</entry>
<entry key="8951">The Status field cannot be a query style enumerated value</entry>
<entry key="8950">Custom style enumerated value must be unique for each choice. The specified value is a duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="8949">Invalid enumerated value style.</entry>
<entry key="8948">Invalid session configuration option.</entry>
<entry key="8947">Invalid license key. Please provide a valid license key</entry>
<entry key="8946">EXTERNAL qualification contains a circular reference</entry>
<entry key="8945">No such object in the parsed XML object list.</entry>
<entry key="8944">XML Parsing error. Invalid character data</entry>
<entry key="8943">XML Parsing error. Invalid enumeration value.</entry>
<entry key="8942">XML Parsing error. Invalid attribute tag.</entry>
<entry key="8941">XML Parsing error. Invalid element tag.</entry>
<entry key="8940">Error during XML definition parsing</entry>
<entry key="4599">No Approval Role form was found</entry>
<entry key="4598">Duplicate Approval Role form found.</entry>
<entry key="4597">No Approval Process Administrator form was found</entry>
<entry key="4596">Duplicate Approval Process Administrator form found.</entry>
<entry key="4595">No Approval More Information form was found</entry>
<entry key="4594">Duplicate Approval More Information form found.</entry>
<entry key="4593">No Approval Alternate form was found</entry>
<entry key="4592">Duplicate Approval Alternate form found.</entry>
<entry key="4591">No Approval Rule Definition form was found</entry>
<entry key="4590">Duplicate Approval Rule Definition form found.</entry>
<entry key="8939">The AR System Plug-In server is not responding.  Cannot connect to the system at this time.  Contact your AR System Administrator for assistance.</entry>
<entry key="8938">Error during Xerces-c Initialization</entry>
<entry key="8937">You do not have permission to the client operation:</entry>
<entry key="8936">Compression of file failed</entry>
<entry key="8935">Upgrade of the server internal forms failed.Only a valid internal form definition can be upgraded.</entry>
<entry key="8934">The proxy fork process could not write information to its log file.</entry>
<entry key="8933">No views were imported.</entry>
<entry key="8932">You do not have write license</entry>
<entry key="8931">Error in semaphore name</entry>
<entry key="8930">The form was not found in the cache</entry>
<entry key="4227">Cannot open the default import log file. (ARERR 4227)</entry>
<entry key="4589">Command requires form and entry ID be specified</entry>
<entry key="4226">Record {0} : a field exceeds the maximum size allowed. (ARERR 4226)</entry>
<entry key="4588">No Approval Process Definition form was found</entry>
<entry key="4587">Duplicate Approval Process Definition form found.</entry>
<entry key="4224">The receiving window was not able to handle the message broadcasted. (ARERR 4224)</entry>
<entry key="4586">No Approval Signature Line form was found</entry>
<entry key="4585">Duplicate Approval Signature Line form found.</entry>
<entry key="4222">No mappings are defined (ARERR 4222)</entry>
<entry key="4584">Duplicate Approval Detail form found.</entry>
<entry key="4583">Unable to open the Approval Server lock file.</entry>
<entry key="4220">The mapping file could not be created. (ARERR 4220)</entry>
<entry key="4582">Another Instance of the Approval Server is already running or the Application Dispatcher is in use.</entry>
<entry key="4581">Memory allocation failed in Approval Server.</entry>
<entry key="4580">The Approval Server is in Limited licensing mode and this form does not have the proper limited license tag.</entry>
<entry key="3134">Logical name {0} is not found in logical mapping form</entry>
<entry key="3133">No Distributed Logical Mapping form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="3132">Two forms contain all the reserved distributed logical mapping fields -- delete one to continue</entry>
<entry key="3131">The reserved distributed pending errors fields can only exist on one form -- delete duplicate to continue.</entry>
<entry key="3130">No Pending Errors form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="8929">Error opening the application violation file (&lt;ar&gt;/db/appl.vio).</entry>
<entry key="8928">Error opening the application audit file (&lt;ar&gt;/db/appl.aud).</entry>
<entry key="8927">The appended text is a message from the external authentication server: error.</entry>
<entry key="8926">The appended text is a message from the external authentication server: note.</entry>
<entry key="8925">The legal value for the RPC socket number for the External Authentication process is 390695</entry>
<entry key="8924">Two or more forms in the workflow form list have duplicate form names.</entry>
<entry key="8923">Unrecognized or misused tag for workflow connection structure</entry>
<entry key="8922">The authentication service is not responding.  Cannot connect to the system at this time.  Contact your AR System Administrator for assistance.</entry>
<entry key="8921">The form list for the workflow contains no forms.</entry>
<entry key="8920">Must specify a form for the workflow to create an active link, filter, or escalation.</entry>
<entry key="4218">Only one -d argument is allowed on the command line. (ARERR 4218)</entry>
<entry key="4579">The Approval Server is in Limited licensing mode and no form associated with this limited license tag is found.</entry>
<entry key="4216">Import completed with errors:\n{0} records were imported; {1} records were not; {2} records were truncated (ARERR 4216)</entry>
<entry key="4578">There are two forms with the same license tag</entry>
<entry key="4577">No Approval Server license -- cannot run the approval engine</entry>
<entry key="4214">\nEnd of {0}'s records\n\n</entry>
<entry key="4212">Import completed successfully:\n{0} records imported; {1} records were truncated (ARERR 4212)</entry>
<entry key="4210">Record {0} : Not enough fields; found {1}, expected {2} (ARERR 4210)</entry>
<entry key="3129">No Distributed Pool form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="3128">The reserved distributed pool fields can only exist on one form - delete duplicate to continue.</entry>
<entry key="3127">Master Flag field is required on source form for transfer with ownership.</entry>
<entry key="3126">Transfer with ownership requires that target form contain "From server" field.</entry>
<entry key="99">The same AR System Server ID is found on two different servers --\nneither will be accessible until one is shut down and tools restarted.</entry>
<entry key="3125">Transfer with ownership requires that target form contain From form field.</entry>
<entry key="98">The Administrator Commands feature is no longer supported</entry>
<entry key="3124">Transfer with ownership requires that target form contain Master Flag field</entry>
<entry key="97">You can connect to only one unlicensed server in a session --\nConnection to the second server is denied.</entry>
<entry key="3123">Must map the Entry ID field to the target Entry ID field, or the From Entry ID field must be present on the target form</entry>
<entry key="96">Capability not supported by this AR System client</entry>
<entry key="3122">The target record for a distributed process (Distributed-Transfer, Distributed-Update, Distributed-Return) no longer exists.</entry>
<entry key="95">RPC and sockets initialization failure</entry>
<entry key="3121">Duplicate entry IDs are encountered during transfer for specified action "Create New" - Target form is missing the required field - "From Request ID"</entry>
<entry key="94">Timeout during database query -- consider using more specific search criteria to narrow the results, and retry the operation</entry>
<entry key="3120">The distributed operation failed because the additional information about the item to be deleted is missing.</entry>
<entry key="93">Timeout during data retrieval due to busy server -- retry the operation</entry>
<entry key="8919">Unable to get next available VUI ID.</entry>
<entry key="92">Timeout during database update -- the operation has been accepted by the server and will usually complete successfully</entry>
<entry key="8918">Unable to update next available VUI ID.</entry>
<entry key="91">RPC call failed</entry>
<entry key="8917">Unable to get next available field ID.</entry>
<entry key="90">Cannot establish a network connection to the AR System server</entry>
<entry key="8916">Unable to update next available field ID.</entry>
<entry key="8915">Insufficient disk space for logging to requested file. Free up disk space before continue.</entry>
<entry key="8914">Workflow logging activated.</entry>
<entry key="8913">A server could not get or lock a semaphore. Make sure that your computer is correctly configured for shared memory and semaphores. If it is, run arsystem stop, and then run arsystem start.</entry>
<entry key="8912">The ARGetListEntryWithFields call is not supported by pre-4.0 AR System server.</entry>
<entry key="8911">Some of the fields have been truncated from the results list because the total length of the fields and separators is greater than the maximum allowed</entry>
<entry key="8910">Field referenced in the qualifier of a table field can not be deleted.</entry>
<entry key="4208">Record {0} : Too many fields; found {1}, expected {2} (ARERR 4208)</entry>
<entry key="4206">Record {0} : "{1}" is not a valid value for field "{2}" (ARERR 4206)</entry>
<entry key="4568">The start or end time provided for the command is not valid</entry>
<entry key="4567">Command requires appropriate parameters</entry>
<entry key="4204">The specified import file contains an improperly formatted record. (ARERR 4204)</entry>
<entry key="4566">No Approval Detail-Signature join form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="4565">No Approval Signature form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="4202">Cannot find form field with saved index (ARERR 4202)</entry>
<entry key="4564">Entry ID specified on command is not valid</entry>
<entry key="4563">Command requires an entry ID specified.</entry>
<entry key="4200">Import file {0} is of an unknown type (ARERR 4200)</entry>
<entry key="4562">Field name specified on command is not valid</entry>
<entry key="4561">Command requires a field name specified.</entry>
<entry key="3119">The transfer or update cannot be performed because transfer mapping is currently disabled.</entry>
<entry key="4560">No Approval Details form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="3118">Failed to record a distributed command.</entry>
<entry key="3117">Update unsuccessful - "From" form or "From" Server field has no value.</entry>
<entry key="3116">Only the master copy of an entry can be transferred</entry>
<entry key="89">No support for join form data calls in the flat file database --\njoin form definition is stored but cannot be used</entry>
<entry key="3115">Unrecognized request pending type.</entry>
<entry key="88">No support for direct SQL commands in the flat file database</entry>
<entry key="3114">The "To" server in mapping definition must be the target server in the attempted mapping.</entry>
<entry key="87">The flat file server is approaching the maximum file size limit (no submissions are allowed after the limit is reached)</entry>
<entry key="3113">The "To" form in mapping definition must be the target form in the attempted mapping.</entry>
<entry key="86">No support for indexing in the flat file database --\nindex definition is stored but not implemented</entry>
<entry key="3112">The "From" server in mapping definition must be the source server in the attempted mapping.</entry>
<entry key="85">You cannot create indexes on a join form or archive form.\nTo index a field, define the index on the base form or source form.</entry>
<entry key="3111">The "From" form in mapping definition must be the source form in the attempted mapping</entry>
<entry key="84">A field with a length greater than 255 bytes cannot be in a sort list.\nTo prevent an error, the field was removed from the sort list.</entry>
<entry key="3110">Two forms contain all the reserved distributed pending fields -- delete one to continue</entry>
<entry key="83">A field with a length greater than 255 bytes cannot be in a result list.</entry>
<entry key="8909">Dialog or Placeholder forms are not allowed in join forms.</entry>
<entry key="82">A field with a length greater than 255 bytes cannot be in an index. </entry>
<entry key="8908">Windows Logon fails.</entry>
<entry key="81">The field is a distributed server reserved field that can be updated only by the distributed server process</entry>
<entry key="8907">Dialog form can only have display-only fields.</entry>
<entry key="80">Delete field failed -- field contents set to NULL and field renamed.</entry>
<entry key="8906">Dialog form cannot have core fields.</entry>
<entry key="8905">Escalations are not allowed on a dialog form.</entry>
<entry key="8904">Filters are not allowed on a dialog form.</entry>
<entry key="8903">The Sort List operation cannot be performed on a dialog form.</entry>
<entry key="8902">The Sort List operation cannot be performed on a dialog form.</entry>
<entry key="8901">The GetListFields operation cannot be performed on a dialog form.</entry>
<entry key="8900">The GetListFields operation cannot be performed on a dialog form.</entry>
<entry key="4559">Assign line error</entry>
<entry key="4558">Qualification line error</entry>
<entry key="4557">Parse set fields command requires two forms be specified</entry>
<entry key="4556">Form name specified on command is not valid</entry>
<entry key="4555">Command requires a form name be specified</entry>
<entry key="4554">An application command failed.</entry>
<entry key="4553">No Application Pending form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="4552">The reserved application pending fields can only exist on one form. - delete duplicates to continue.</entry>
<entry key="4551">Must be Application Server user to perform this operation</entry>
<entry key="3109">No Distributed Pending form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="4550">Creation of an application form failed.</entry>
<entry key="3108">Two forms contain all the reserved distributed mapping fields -- delete one to continue</entry>
<entry key="3107">No Distributed Mapping form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="3106">The server being accessed is not licensed for the Distributed Server Option</entry>
<entry key="79">Request for unique setting on database index has been ignored for fields of this type</entry>
<entry key="78">A full text token has become available and has been allocated to you --\naccess has been upgraded to allow full text searching</entry>
<entry key="77">No free floating full text license tokens are available.\nCurrently accessing the system without full text search capability.\nLicense will upgrade when one is available.</entry>
<entry key="3103">Memory allocation for the DSO process failed.</entry>
<entry key="76">A write token has become available and has been allocated to you --\naccess has been upgraded to write access</entry>
<entry key="3102">An instance of the Distributed Server is already running.</entry>
<entry key="75">No free floating write license tokens are available.\nCurrently accessing the system in read-only mode.\nLicense will upgrade when one is available.</entry>
<entry key="3101">Failed to open the Distributed Server lock file ar.lck.390601.</entry>
<entry key="74">A duplicate index has been specified --\nduplicate was omitted.</entry>
<entry key="3100">This AR System is not licensed for the Distributed Server Option</entry>
<entry key="73">A change to the Submitter mode setting does not take effect until AR System is shut down and restarted. </entry>
<entry key="72">The query matched more than the maximum number of entries specified by the server</entry>
<entry key="71">Only the Administrator has access to this active link.</entry>
<entry key="70">The character menu referenced by one or more fields in this form does not exist.</entry>
<entry key="4549">The supplied password is invalid for the user performing the operation.</entry>
<entry key="69">Creation of one of the SQL views for the form failed within the SQL database.\nForm is created successfully, but the SQL view is not in place.</entry>
<entry key="68">RPC environment variable is out of legal range\n(390600, 390603, 390619 - 390669, 390680 - 390694).\nNOTE: The value 390603 and the range 390619 - 390669 are specialty servers\nand may have restricted functionality.</entry>
<entry key="67">Not able to open the menu.</entry>
<entry key="66">The query matched more than the maximum number of entries specified for retrieval</entry>
<entry key="65">Multiple form links are not supported in new filter definition syntax.\nOnly the first link is loaded.</entry>
<entry key="64">The filter/escalation action cannot write to the specified log file --\naction created but not logged in the log file.</entry>
<entry key="63">One or more values in the statistic operation cannot be retrieved due to permission restrictions.\nThose values are excluded from the statistics computation.</entry>
<entry key="62">You do not have access to the requested record.</entry>
<entry key="2009">No servers are specified on the command line or in the AR System directory file</entry>
<entry key="61">You do not have read access to this field on this record.</entry>
<entry key="2008">Invalid command line options</entry>
<entry key="60">You do not have read access to field</entry>
<entry key="2007">Cannot read data file</entry>
<entry key="2006">Failure while retrieving entries from the server directory file</entry>
<entry key="2005">No servers are currently accessible</entry>
<entry key="2004">Cannot initialize the AR System</entry>
<entry key="2003">Cannot connect to the X server</entry>
<entry key="2002">Cannot read the configuration file --\nARHOME environment variable may be set incorrectly</entry>
<entry key="2001">Cannot allocate memory</entry>
<entry key="9099">The AR System Multi-Form Search form cannot be used for updating</entry>
<entry key="9098">Server License fields can only exist on one form. Delete the duplicate form </entry>
<entry key="9097">Cannot find the Server License form</entry>
<entry key="9096">Value specified for the Authentication Chaining Mode is outside the valid range of 0 - 4</entry>
<entry key="9095">Subadministrator roles permissions have been removed from the object because the object is not in a deployable application</entry>
<entry key="9094">Subadministrator group permissions have been removed from the object because the object is in a deployable application</entry>
<entry key="9093">User is currently connected from another machine.</entry>
<entry key="9092">The pending file is corrupt.</entry>
<entry key="9091">User data is corrupted.  License deleted</entry>
<entry key="9090">Cannot change license type of a user to Fixed more than 3 times in 1 week</entry>
<entry key="59">Your login failed, but connected as a guest user.</entry>
<entry key="399">Error in definition for an active link</entry>
<entry key="57">One or more fields in the statistic operation had a NULL value.\nThose values are excluded from the statistics computation.</entry>
<entry key="398">Unable to obtain the memory for cache.</entry>
<entry key="56">Entry does not exists on form</entry>
<entry key="397">Reserved field GroupList exceeds the 4000 character limit.</entry>
<entry key="55">The following item was not imported</entry>
<entry key="396">Support file for the specified object can not be found.</entry>
<entry key="54">No changes have been specified for the update operation</entry>
<entry key="395">The system has timed out while waiting for a process to return a value.</entry>
<entry key="53">Administrator access required to get permission information</entry>
<entry key="394">AR System is currently in Administrator Only mode. Please retry your operation later.</entry>
<entry key="52">The field is a core system field and cannot be changed</entry>
<entry key="393">Status-History field cannot be used as labelField or valueField in the query menu</entry>
<entry key="51">Field ID specified does not exist in this form</entry>
<entry key="392">Field/VUI name must be unique for the form -- there is already a field or VUI using this name</entry>
<entry key="50">You have no permission to this field.</entry>
<entry key="391">Creation of VUI failed</entry>
<entry key="390">Cannot delete the default VUI for a form --\nall forms require at least one VUI.</entry>
<entry key="2358">Set Failed</entry>
<entry key="2357">Get Failed</entry>
<entry key="2356">You have entered a value in an real number field \nwhich is outside of the valid range for real numbers</entry>
<entry key="2355">There is already an Active Link in this form with this name:</entry>
<entry key="2354">You have not entered data for any of your fields --\nenter data for at least one field before pressing the Apply button.</entry>
<entry key="2353">You do not have permission to perform Distributed Server operations</entry>
<entry key="2352">One of your mapping servers is not available or does not exist</entry>
<entry key="2351">Invalid mapping definition -- respecify your custom mapping</entry>
<entry key="2350">Duplicate mapping name -- rename your distributed mapping</entry>
<entry key="9089">User data is corrupted</entry>
<entry key="9088">The import file does not hold an application definition.</entry>
<entry key="9085">Host IP address not found</entry>
<entry key="9084">User is currently connected from another machine</entry>
<entry key="9083">Cannot find the Application Statistics Configuration form</entry>
<entry key="9082">Application Statistics fields can only exist on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="9081">Cannot find the Application Statistics form</entry>
<entry key="9080">Application Statistics fields can only exist on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="49">Internal error: The request ID is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="48">Insufficient space for the response to be returned(minimum of 4096 bytes).</entry>
<entry key="389">Duplicate VUI for the form</entry>
<entry key="47">Email notification operation timed out before completion</entry>
<entry key="388">VUI does not exist for the specified form</entry>
<entry key="46">Message action and Log action in else branch are not supported for escalations</entry>
<entry key="387">Updating this entry will violate join condition</entry>
<entry key="386">Exception occurred while handling previous exception</entry>
<entry key="44">You have exceeded the maximum number of forms allowed under the current server license.</entry>
<entry key="385">The same ID was specified several times in a "multiple" operation API call --\neach ID specified for this call must be unique.</entry>
<entry key="43">Unable to retrieve the menu for character field "field name".</entry>
<entry key="384">The name specified contains an invalid character.  Only printable characters are allowed.</entry>
<entry key="42">Server not licensed to run with multiple-RPC sockets --\nignoring setting and continuing</entry>
<entry key="383">File menu contains too many items on one level (maximum 1000)</entry>
<entry key="41">Unrecognized command line argument -- ignoring command line and continuing</entry>
<entry key="382">The value(s) for this entry violate a unique index that has been defined for this form</entry>
<entry key="381">Multiple entries match filter conditions --\nthis operation has been defined so that "Multiple Match" generate an error.</entry>
<entry key="2349">You have entered a value in an integer field \nwhich is outside of the valid range for integers</entry>
<entry key="380">No item matches filter conditions --\nthis operation has been defined so that "No Match" generates an error.</entry>
<entry key="2348">Field data type and assignment data type are not compatible</entry>
<entry key="2347">Missing button data</entry>
<entry key="2346">Query menu not expanded</entry>
<entry key="2345">Cannot expand menu {0} for field {1}</entry>
<entry key="2344">Export errors</entry>
<entry key="2343">Selection values must be unique</entry>
<entry key="2342">Invalid macro definition file format</entry>
<entry key="2341">Invalid parameter specification in the DDE assign line</entry>
<entry key="2340">Too many levels in nested macro</entry>
<entry key="9079">Server Statistics fields can only exist on one form. Delete the duplicate</entry>
<entry key="9078">Cannot find the Server Statistics form</entry>
<entry key="9077">Server Events fields can only exist on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="9076">Cannot find the Server Events form</entry>
<entry key="9075">Problem encountered during creation of one of the server system forms</entry>
<entry key="4513">No Approval Form form was found</entry>
<entry key="4512">No Approval Notification form was found</entry>
<entry key="9072">Only one form can contain the Role form fields</entry>
<entry key="4511">No Approval Administration form was found</entry>
<entry key="9071">Only one form can contain the Group form fields</entry>
<entry key="4510">Two or more roles have the same name</entry>
<entry key="9070">Only one form can contain the User form fields</entry>
<entry key="39">Filter/escalation 'set field' process timed out before completion </entry>
<entry key="38">Filter/escalation 'set field' process returned an error. \nThe current transaction is rejected. No update to the database occurs.</entry>
<entry key="379">Problem encountered during creation of one of the distributed forms</entry>
<entry key="37">Error while accessing one of the debug trace files. \nDebug tracing to the file is disabled.</entry>
<entry key="378">Must be Distributed Server to perform this operation</entry>
<entry key="36">The database is not the expected version (may need to run upgrade program)</entry>
<entry key="377">The distributed or application operation specified in the filter Run Process action contains mismatched quotes</entry>
<entry key="35">Another copy of the server is already running on the same RPC socket</entry>
<entry key="376">Cannot update this entry -- this distributed entry is not the master copy</entry>
<entry key="34">Error while opening the AR System server lock file</entry>
<entry key="375">Duplicate distributed mapping name</entry>
<entry key="33">AR System failed to start a process. \nMake sure that your system is not low on resources.</entry>
<entry key="374">Distributed mapping does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="32">AR System server terminated normally</entry>
<entry key="373">Must be administrator to access the distributed mapping</entry>
<entry key="31">The new user was issued a fixed license of the following type</entry>
<entry key="372">Could not create alert event</entry>
<entry key="30">You are already at the limit of the number of fixed user licenses of the following type</entry>
<entry key="371">You cannot change the value of the Submitter field --\nthe "Submitter Mode" of the system is configured to be locked</entry>
<entry key="2339">Delete failed</entry>
<entry key="370">No form ID for the form</entry>
<entry key="2338">Cannot change type of an existing action</entry>
<entry key="2337">The field ID is too big</entry>
<entry key="2336">There are no If actions defined.  Please create at least one If action.</entry>
<entry key="2335">Total width of your fields exceeds the maximum</entry>
<entry key="2334">You must select a form</entry>
<entry key="2333">Invalid file format</entry>
<entry key="2332">One of the field names is invalid</entry>
<entry key="2331">An error has occurred while formatting your diary text</entry>
<entry key="2330">You have no user specified in your configuration file --\nuse the Login option under the File menu to login as an Administrator</entry>
<entry key="4503">AR System Application server restarting</entry>
<entry key="9063">Server allows only Unicode clients (except Administrator and Alert tools).</entry>
<entry key="4502">Operation cancelled due to error</entry>
<entry key="1243">Duplicate name for View!\nDo you want to overwrite the existing view?</entry>
<entry key="9062">Failed to convert from Unicode format to character data.</entry>
<entry key="4501">AR System Application server terminated -- fatal error encountered</entry>
<entry key="1242">You can continue with out of date customized view files or they can be reloaded from the server.  Do you wish to reload the form from the server?  Selecting Continue will lose your customized view.</entry>
<entry key="9061">Failed to convert the Character data to Unicode format.</entry>
<entry key="4500">AR System Application server terminated when a signal/exception was received by the server</entry>
<entry key="1241">The administrator has updated this form on an AR System 2.1 server.  Your customized view cannot be updated using this tool.  If you continue, you may encounter some problems.  Do you wish to continue?</entry>
<entry key="9060">A system error prevented the Unicode converter from being opened.</entry>
<entry key="1240">The customized view for this form has been updated to AR System 3.0 format.  Because of version translation limitations, you may need to reposition some buttons using Customize View.</entry>
<entry key="29">The AR Server license is a Demo license that expires</entry>
<entry key="28">The demo license for this AR Server has expired. \nPlease contact your distributor for license information.</entry>
<entry key="369">Must be administrator to access the escalation</entry>
<entry key="27">This COPY of the Action Request System(R) does not have authorization key set, but is ready for use or evaluation. \nFor unlimited capabilities, contact your sales representative.</entry>
<entry key="368">Error in definition for an escalation</entry>
<entry key="26">Administrator operations are disabled on this server</entry>
<entry key="367">Duplicate escalation name</entry>
<entry key="25">Fields in 'set fields' action do not exist in the target form.</entry>
<entry key="366">Escalation does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="24">Failure while trying to run the filter/escalation process</entry>
<entry key="23">Open/write to the filter/escalation log file resumed successfully</entry>
<entry key="364">Diary field cannot be set to a NULL value in a filter/escalation</entry>
<entry key="22">Failure during open/write to the filter/escalation log file, logging to the log file is suspended.</entry>
<entry key="363">Required field assigned $DEFAULT$ but there is no default value for the field</entry>
<entry key="21">AR System server terminated - fatal error occurred in ARSERVER</entry>
<entry key="362">The flat file server has hit the maximum file size limit.  No more entries can be created.</entry>
<entry key="20">AR System server terminated when a signal/exception was received by the server</entry>
<entry key="361">An unqualified search was issued and the server has been configured to disallow unqualified searches.\nYou must specify some search criteria to perform a search on this form</entry>
<entry key="2329">No administrator macros are defined</entry>
<entry key="360">No currency conversion ratio exists for the requested conversion</entry>
<entry key="2328">You do not have a known server specified in your configuration file --\nthe tool will default to the first server specified in your directory file</entry>
<entry key="2326">You have specified a field ID already in use</entry>
<entry key="2325">Field IDs below 100 are reserved for core fields</entry>
<entry key="2324">The internal field length cannot be less than zero</entry>
<entry key="2323">Unrecognized arithmetic operation</entry>
<entry key="2322">You have entered a non-digit character for a numeric field</entry>
<entry key="2321">You have entered an improperly formatted value for a real field</entry>
<entry key="2320">Qualification line error at position</entry>
<entry key="9059">The join form contains a circular reference</entry>
<entry key="1239">Duplicate macro name</entry>
<entry key="9058">Update of Localized Active Link or Menu failed</entry>
<entry key="9057">Recursion of localized queries are not allowed</entry>
<entry key="9056">The server is not localized</entry>
<entry key="4857">Line item index out of bounds for this Purchase Requisition</entry>
<entry key="1598">This application does not support customization of views of pre-Action Request System(R) 3.0 forms.  Such views can still be customized using previous versions of this application.</entry>
<entry key="9055">The VUI import file is in an incorrect format</entry>
<entry key="4856">Could not find the Purchase Requisition-Line Item form</entry>
<entry key="1597">Import operation failed (but continuing) on data row</entry>
<entry key="9054">The specified field does not exist in the form</entry>
<entry key="4855">Command requires form and entry ID be specified</entry>
<entry key="1596">Import operation terminated on data row</entry>
<entry key="9053">The default VUI specified in the schema import file was not found. The default VUI was redefined to a pre-existing VUI from the form</entry>
<entry key="4854">Command requires entry ID, tag, and other</entry>
<entry key="1595">Format of contents of import file inconsistent with format type</entry>
<entry key="1233">Your disk drive is about full, please remove unwanted files</entry>
<entry key="9052">The VUI is not unique for the form. The label, locale, and platform properties of this VUI must be unique to the form</entry>
<entry key="4853">Command requires entry ID</entry>
<entry key="1594">Unrecognized import file type</entry>
<entry key="1232">Macro recording is active -- modifications will be made to the entry\nbut will not be recorded in the macro</entry>
<entry key="9051">Multiple Message Catalogs exist.  There must only be one Message Catalog</entry>
<entry key="4852">Failure while updating a line item in the purchase requisition</entry>
<entry key="1593">Must specify a filename</entry>
<entry key="9050">Localization has been turned on but no Message Catalog exists</entry>
<entry key="4851">Failure while splitting line items from the purchase requisition</entry>
<entry key="1592">Cannot translate the group name in the Group list field</entry>
<entry key="1230">The selected user command definition will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="4850">Pending ID is required when run in one command mode</entry>
<entry key="1591">Not enough information to parse the assignment string</entry>
<entry key="1590">Format of time value is not recognized</entry>
<entry key="359">Set/Create/Delete operations to definition are only supported on RPC socket 390600.</entry>
<entry key="358">Error while accessing a menu file on the server</entry>
<entry key="357">Character menu contains too many items on one level (maximum 99)</entry>
<entry key="356">Duplicate character menu name</entry>
<entry key="3403">Unable to terminate web service for authentication.</entry>
<entry key="355">Must be administrator to access the filter</entry>
<entry key="3402">Unable to initialize web service for authentication.</entry>
<entry key="354">You have no access to administrator command</entry>
<entry key="3401">External authentication destination URL not configured.</entry>
<entry key="353">You have no access to form</entry>
<entry key="3400">Unable to access server configuration file</entry>
<entry key="352">Notification to special Submitter or Assignee group specified.\nReference to the Submitter or Assignee group exists in the\nreferenced Submitter or Assigned-to field.\nNotification canceled to avoid a potential infinite loop.</entry>
<entry key="351">Cannot specify qualification on password field</entry>
<entry key="2319">Assign line error at position</entry>
<entry key="350">Attempt to divide by zero (0) in arithmetic operation</entry>
<entry key="2318">Error encountered -- cannot create Set Fields screen</entry>
<entry key="2317">Unrecognized group in group list or group list longer than maximum allowed</entry>
<entry key="2316">An arithmetic operation was expected</entry>
<entry key="2315">Select an execution condition for your active link</entry>
<entry key="2314">Select a field for your 'Execute On' condition</entry>
<entry key="2313">Enter an active link name</entry>
<entry key="2312">You must select a form</entry>
<entry key="2311">You have created the maximum number of active link actions allowed</entry>
<entry key="2310">Error encountered writing to file</entry>
<entry key="1229">The selected custom report definition will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="9048">Encrypt data at rest key is corrupt. Please contact Administrator.</entry>
<entry key="4849">No purchase request ID field or field contains a bad value for line item</entry>
<entry key="1228">The selected macro definition will be deleted</entry>
<entry key="9047">Query set source is empty.</entry>
<entry key="4848">No line number field or field contains a bad value for line item</entry>
<entry key="1589">Format for status history reference is invalid</entry>
<entry key="1227">Failure trying to expand the character menu</entry>
<entry key="9046">Query set source has to be the only source in the list of query sources.</entry>
<entry key="4847">Line Item Mapback command requires form to be the line item form</entry>
<entry key="1588">Value specified for selection not one of defined values for this field</entry>
<entry key="1226">Exit User Tool?</entry>
<entry key="9045">Operand in sort by clause is not included in the select list operands.</entry>
<entry key="4846">A value for Supplier for each line is required to split line items</entry>
<entry key="1587">Unknown field referenced in query line</entry>
<entry key="1225">Duplicate name for user command\nDo you want to overwrite the existing user command?</entry>
<entry key="1586">Expected a closing parenthesis at this point</entry>
<entry key="1224">Duplicate name for custom report\nDo you want to overwrite the existing custom report?</entry>
<entry key="4844">Line Item Map command requires form to be the purchase request form</entry>
<entry key="1585">Too many nested levels of parentheses in command</entry>
<entry key="1223">Duplicate name for macro\nDo you want to overwrite the existing macro?</entry>
<entry key="4843">Row count on part is inconsistent with definition of part</entry>
<entry key="1584">Expected a field or value at this point</entry>
<entry key="1222">Unable to find help for the specified field</entry>
<entry key="4842">Part type value is unrecognized</entry>
<entry key="1583">Expected a relational operation at this point</entry>
<entry key="1221">The specified file already exists</entry>
<entry key="4841">Error while attempting to open a parts catalog file</entry>
<entry key="1582">Expected a logical operation at this point</entry>
<entry key="1220">You have not saved changes on the exploded help window --\nthey will not be included in the current operation if you continue</entry>
<entry key="4840">A category was specified that does not exist</entry>
<entry key="1581">Unexpected character at this location in the query line</entry>
<entry key="1580">Missing closing quote on a character string/name</entry>
<entry key="349">Cannot delete a core field</entry>
<entry key="348">Group definition is empty -- no access to database is possible.</entry>
<entry key="347">You have no access to active link</entry>
<entry key="346">Active link does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="345">Duplicate active link name</entry>
<entry key="344">Group type or category conflict between two groups with the same group ID</entry>
<entry key="343">Invalid filter definition.</entry>
<entry key="342">The AR System directory file could not be opened.</entry>
<entry key="341">Set Fields process failed.</entry>
<entry key="2309">Resulting filename is longer than maximum allowed</entry>
<entry key="340">Incorrect format for the status history field</entry>
<entry key="2308">You have created the maximum number of filter actions allowed</entry>
<entry key="2307">Only fields existing on the server can be copied</entry>
<entry key="2306">Error during character menu delete operation</entry>
<entry key="2305">Selection fields require one or more values</entry>
<entry key="2304">Enter data</entry>
<entry key="2303">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2301">Specify a directory and filename</entry>
<entry key="2300">Format of time value is not recognized</entry>
<entry key="1219">You have not saved changes on the exploded help window --\nthey will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="4839">The part record does not have a parent category</entry>
<entry key="1218">A Set Field action was attempted --\nyou are on a Display window so no action was taken</entry>
<entry key="4838">Malloc failed in Purchase Request server</entry>
<entry key="1579">Cannot use selection value name in Status History --\nyou do not have access to Status</entry>
<entry key="1217">You have not saved changes on a diary or text edit window --\nthey will not be included in the current apply if you continue</entry>
<entry key="4837">Catalog command requires form to be the parts form</entry>
<entry key="1216">This operation will modify {0} entries.\n\nDo you wish to continue?</entry>
<entry key="4836">Entry ID (0 is top level) or category tag is required for this command.</entry>
<entry key="1215">Server cannot set to the client locale. Locale sensitive operation done on the server may not conform to the client's locale convention</entry>
<entry key="1214">Macro recording is active --\noperation recorded but no database operation performed</entry>
<entry key="1213">Multiple entries match qualification criteria --\nInformation pulled from first matching entry</entry>
<entry key="1574">Filename is longer than maximum allowed</entry>
<entry key="1212">Query window is now connected to a different form --\ncontinuing will change the current form</entry>
<entry key="1211">You have not saved changes on a diary or text edit window --\nthey will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="4831">The tag is not associated with any form.</entry>
<entry key="1572">Cannot create new item</entry>
<entry key="1210">You have not saved changes on the properties screen --\nthey will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="4830">Same tag is associated with more than one form. This is not allowed.</entry>
<entry key="339">Incorrect format for a diary field</entry>
<entry key="338">Duplicate Entry ID found", and the current setting is "Do Not Create New".</entry>
<entry key="337">You have reached the maximum number of database entries permitted with this version of the Action Request System(R).\nTo purchase the unrestricted version, contact your sales representative.</entry>
<entry key="699">Full text search attributes cannot be specified for multi-form search system form</entry>
<entry key="336">Cannot assign a user to the special Submitter (3), Assignee (4), Assignee Group (7), Dynamic, or Computed groups</entry>
<entry key="698">Full Text MFS Category Name must be unique on a form -- there is already a field using this name</entry>
<entry key="335">Format for an AR System reserved field is invalid</entry>
<entry key="697">You can only use the Full Text Indexed fields as the Weighted relevancy fields for Multi-Form Search on a form</entry>
<entry key="334">AR System reserved field definition cannot be modified.</entry>
<entry key="696">The field needs to have public permissions to be a full text Multi-Form Search Category or Title field</entry>
<entry key="333">You have no access to field</entry>
<entry key="695">Full Text MFS Category Name property can only be specified for a Character field.</entry>
<entry key="332">You do not have write access to the field before the record is saved.</entry>
<entry key="694">The AR System Multi-Form Search form cannot be used for the specified operation</entry>
<entry key="331">You do not have write access to this record.</entry>
<entry key="693">Update operation is not allowed on AR System Multi-Form Search form.</entry>
<entry key="330">You do not have write access to this field.</entry>
<entry key="692">Full text license is required for Multi-form search feature.</entry>
<entry key="691">Either the Form List is empty or forms do not have any FTS fields in the AR System Multi-Form Search form</entry>
<entry key="690">No search term specified in the AR System Multi-Form Search form</entry>
<entry key="1209">You have not saved changes on this screen --\nthey will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="1208">You have not saved changes on this screen --\nthey will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="1569">Empty macro definition</entry>
<entry key="1207">A recording operation is in progress --\ncurrent recording will be lost if you continue</entry>
<entry key="9026">Could not decode bytes into string for UTF-8 charset.</entry>
<entry key="1206">You are invited to evaluate the Action Request System(R) without purchasing or activating licenses. To obtain a license for production use please contact your AR System administrator. The AR System server without a license is:</entry>
<entry key="9025">Provider does not support hashing algorithm.</entry>
<entry key="1567">Unrecognized operation while loading a custom report format</entry>
<entry key="1205">New fields/active links added/made accessible by Administrator --\nadded as hidden fields to local view file</entry>
<entry key="9024">Ignored field permission granular overlay type and reset it to No Overlay.</entry>
<entry key="1566">No custom report formats are defined</entry>
<entry key="1204">Partial selections will become full selections on playback</entry>
<entry key="9023">Association with Many to Many cardinality can not be followed for archiving.</entry>
<entry key="1565">Second part of statistics operation missing or invalid</entry>
<entry key="1203">This record has been updated by another user since you retrieved it</entry>
<entry key="9022">Ignoring request to archive entries with invalid age.</entry>
<entry key="1202">A recording operation is in progress --\nyour current recording will be lost if you exit</entry>
<entry key="9021">An error occurred while performing archived data management.</entry>
<entry key="1563">Enter a directory to store the command in</entry>
<entry key="1201">New text longer than the maximum allowed length -- truncating to fit</entry>
<entry key="9020">FIPS mode requires the security policy to be "encryption required".</entry>
<entry key="4821">TGP specified in data, but no group form</entry>
<entry key="1562">Second part of report operation missing or invalid</entry>
<entry key="1200">No matching entries (or no permission to entries) for qualification criteria</entry>
<entry key="4820">Insufficient memory for Set Up and Move server.</entry>
<entry key="329">Invalid password or authentication string.</entry>
<entry key="328">Duplicate command name.</entry>
<entry key="327">Incorrect data type for statistic operation.</entry>
<entry key="689">At least one field in the forms being searched is in the process of being indexed which may effect the search results</entry>
<entry key="326">Required field cannot be blank.</entry>
<entry key="688">Only one form can contain the Multi-Form Search fields</entry>
<entry key="325">Duplicate filter name</entry>
<entry key="687">Table field cannot be indexed for multi-form search because the qualification contains an external qualifier and/or display-only fields</entry>
<entry key="324">Administrator command does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="686">A re-indexing will be performed for each full text indexed field on the form at the specified time(s) in place of an update scan due to the absence of a last modified time field (field ID 6) on the form</entry>
<entry key="323">Filter does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="685">FTS Plugin is not available -- will retry connection.</entry>
<entry key="322">Invalid hierarchy in character menu definition</entry>
<entry key="684">You have provided an invalid value in the Document Boost field for Full Text Indexing purpose</entry>
<entry key="321">Too many levels in character menu definition</entry>
<entry key="683">Full text search is disabled because it is not configured properly; a database search will be performed</entry>
<entry key="320">Menu does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="682">Full text search service not available; a database search was performed</entry>
<entry key="681">Due to the field length change, the corresponding full text index is being rebuilt.</entry>
<entry key="680">Full Text Search User Licenses are available but the Full Text Search engine is not installed or installed incorrectly.</entry>
<entry key="9019">Client cannot connect to this FIPS-noncompliant server because the client is connected to a server that enforces FIPS.</entry>
<entry key="9018">Client cannot connect to this FIPS-compliant server because the client is connected to a server that does not enforce FIPS.</entry>
<entry key="9017">FIPS encryption failed</entry>
<entry key="1559">Problem with macro/custom report</entry>
<entry key="9016">An error occurred with the decryption because the CRC is invalid</entry>
<entry key="1558">Create of user command failed -- file system problem</entry>
<entry key="9015">To encrypt/decrypt a null string is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="1557">Enter a command string to execute</entry>
<entry key="9014">The encrypted string is greater than the maximum length allowed</entry>
<entry key="9013">The encryption license does not match the encryption library</entry>
<entry key="1555">Enter a command name</entry>
<entry key="9012">Encryption is not licensed on the AR System server</entry>
<entry key="9011">Loading of encryption library failed</entry>
<entry key="1553">Cannot locate your selected command</entry>
<entry key="9010">The encryption library was not found and cannot be loaded</entry>
<entry key="4810">Duplicate category names found.</entry>
<entry key="1550">No macros are defined</entry>
<entry key="319">Specified field length exceeds the max limit.</entry>
<entry key="318">Group does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="317">Duplicate form name</entry>
<entry key="679">Form based search is not allowed without a full text license or while full text searching is disabled</entry>
<entry key="316">Failed to create the temporary file.</entry>
<entry key="678">Full text indexing is disabled --\nturn on full text indexing and retry your operation</entry>
<entry key="315">Form/field to delete contains data, please confirm the deletion.</entry>
<entry key="677">License type can only be 0 (none), 1 (fixed), 2 (floating), or 3 (restricted read)</entry>
<entry key="314">Field does not exist on current form</entry>
<entry key="313">Incompatible data types for intended relational operation.</entry>
<entry key="675">FTS home directory can only be set by the installer, and not by using arsetfulltextinfo API call.</entry>
<entry key="312">Incompatible data types for intended arithmetic operation.</entry>
<entry key="674">The search query matched too many words in the FTS dictionary.</entry>
<entry key="311">Field ID specified is not found on this form.</entry>
<entry key="673">The query compares two fields that involve full text indexed fields.\nThe full text search capability does not support comparing two fields.\nThe comparison will be made using the functionality of the database.</entry>
<entry key="310">Value has wrong data type for the field</entry>
<entry key="672">Status History field can not be indexed for Full Text Search.</entry>
<entry key="671">The indexer for running the Full Text Search indexing can not be found.</entry>
<entry key="670">The full text search index on this field is being created but may take some time to finish. Default search is used for now.</entry>
<entry key="9009">XDR xres error during XDR encoding</entry>
<entry key="9008">The size of the memory buffer used in XDR (external data representation) is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="9007">The specified data key encryption algorithm is not supported by the encryption library</entry>
<entry key="1549">Modify All operation failed during operation on entry with ID</entry>
<entry key="9006">The specified public key encryption algorithm is not supported by the encryption library</entry>
<entry key="9005">An error occurred in the encryption library</entry>
<entry key="1547">You have entered a value for a numeric field that is either too large or too small</entry>
<entry key="9004">Error during symmetric key data decryption</entry>
<entry key="1546">You have entered a non-digit character for a numeric field</entry>
<entry key="9003">Error during public key data decryption</entry>
<entry key="1545">You have entered an improperly formatted value for a real field</entry>
<entry key="9002">The data encryption key exchange failed</entry>
<entry key="1544">Value specified for field name not numeric or not a field</entry>
<entry key="9001">Encryption is required by the AR System server</entry>
<entry key="1543">A field name is required for all operations except count</entry>
<entry key="9000">Encryption is disallowed by the AR System server</entry>
<entry key="1540">Create of macro/custom report failed -- file system problems</entry>
<entry key="309">The entry you are working on was modified by another user after the last time you retrieved it.</entry>
<entry key="308">Duplicate field in the field list.</entry>
<entry key="307">Required field can not be blank.</entry>
<entry key="669">The Destination full text index directory already exists.</entry>
<entry key="306">Value does not fall within the limits specified for the field</entry>
<entry key="668">Invalid full text search query.</entry>
<entry key="305">Next available ID length exceeds the Entry ID field length --\ncontact the Administrator.</entry>
<entry key="667">Full text operations are enabled --\nturn off full text operations and retry your operation</entry>
<entry key="304">Must have Administrative permissions to perform this operation</entry>
<entry key="666">Full text operations are disabled --\nturn on full text operations and retry your operation</entry>
<entry key="303">Form does not exist on server</entry>
<entry key="665">This server does not have a Full Text Search license.</entry>
<entry key="302">Entry does not exist in database</entry>
<entry key="664">Full text not allowed with earlier version of a flat file database</entry>
<entry key="301">Error while writing to a file</entry>
<entry key="663">Full text search can not be done on a field that is not a character, diary, or attachment field.</entry>
<entry key="300">Insufficient server memory for running this process.</entry>
<entry key="662">Operation requested is too large for a single full text search command</entry>
<entry key="661">Failed to relocate full text index directory. </entry>
<entry key="660">An error occurred while updating the "Ignore Word" file.</entry>
<entry key="1539">Cannot specify a count operation with a column layout without specifying a field name</entry>
<entry key="1536">Please supply a name for your macro/custom report</entry>
<entry key="1535">Problem querying servers</entry>
<entry key="1534">Must specify a user name</entry>
<entry key="1533">Problem formatting diary entry</entry>
<entry key="1531">X and/or Y coordinates are out of range</entry>
<entry key="1530">Update of custom operation failed</entry>
<entry key="659">An error has occurred while opening the "Ignore Word" file.</entry>
<entry key="658">Failed to read full text documents</entry>
<entry key="657">Unable to complete the full text search operation.</entry>
<entry key="656">Unable to connect to the full text database</entry>
<entry key="655">ARFullTextInfoRequestList list is empty.</entry>
<entry key="654">Unrecognized full text information tag</entry>
<entry key="653">The Full text information data for this tag is invalid. </entry>
<entry key="652">The Full text information data for this tag has an incompatible data type or the value is out of range.</entry>
<entry key="651">ARFullTextInfoList list is empty</entry>
<entry key="1529">Status field is not accessible -- cannot display Status History</entry>
<entry key="1528">Column headers will not fit within the space defined between top and bottom margins -- total number of lines increased to the following value</entry>
<entry key="1527">Total number of characters per line (including margins) is greater than maximum of 4096</entry>
<entry key="1526">Total number of characters per line (between margins) less than minimum of 40</entry>
<entry key="1525">Total number of lines (between margins) less than minimum of five</entry>
<entry key="1524">Unrecognized selection value</entry>
<entry key="1522">Definition file format problem: active link definition</entry>
<entry key="1521">Definition file format problem: begin active link</entry>
<entry key="1520">Definition file format problem: invalid form/active link end</entry>
<entry key="649">Recurrence Start Time must be less than Recurrence End Time.</entry>
<entry key="648">Level 1 Time Segments must be 'Available' and Level 2 must be 'Unavailable'.</entry>
<entry key="647">No Business Time Segment-Entity Association form could be found on the server.</entry>
<entry key="646">The reserved Segment-Entity Association fields exist on multiple forms. They are only allowed on one form.</entry>
<entry key="645">The level specified has to be from 1 to 1000</entry>
<entry key="644">The specified Time Segment does not exist in the Business Time Segment form.</entry>
<entry key="643">No Time Segment form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="642">The reserved Time Segment fields exist on multiple forms. They are only allowed to exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="641">Open hours must be included in the workday schedule definition.</entry>
<entry key="640">No workday definition exists with the specified tag</entry>
<entry key="1519">Definition file format problem with character menus</entry>
<entry key="1518">Definition file format problem: field definition</entry>
<entry key="1517">Definition file format problem: field clause</entry>
<entry key="1516">Definition file format problem: missing form name</entry>
<entry key="1515">Definition file format problem: invalid form name</entry>
<entry key="1513">View file format problem: active link definition</entry>
<entry key="1512">View file format problem: begin active link</entry>
<entry key="1511">View file format problem: invalid form/active link end</entry>
<entry key="1510">View file format problem: field definition</entry>
<entry key="639">No Workday form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="638">Two forms contain all the reserved workday fields -- delete one to continue</entry>
<entry key="999">Unable to free shared or exclusive lock</entry>
<entry key="637">No holiday definition exists with the specified tag</entry>
<entry key="998">Unable to free shared or exclusive lock on user cache hash list</entry>
<entry key="636">No Holiday form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="635">The reserved holiday fields exist on multiple forms. They are only allowed to exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="1509">View file format problem: field clause</entry>
<entry key="1508">View file format problem: missing form name</entry>
<entry key="1507">View file format problem: invalid form name</entry>
<entry key="1506">Problems creating new field</entry>
<entry key="1505">Unrecognized field type (defaulting to text)</entry>
<entry key="1504">Only selection data types can be displayed using exclusive choice boxes (defaulting to text)</entry>
<entry key="1503">Only selection data types can be displayed using checkboxes (defaulting to text)</entry>
<entry key="1502">Only integer data types can be displayed using numeric text (defaulting to text)</entry>
<entry key="1501">Cannot record operation:</entry>
<entry key="1500">Out of memory</entry>
<entry key="989">Cannot create or modify a currency field without specifying at least one functional currency</entry>
<entry key="988">Currency part must be specified to use currency field in this context</entry>
<entry key="626">Time in the workday definition is invalid</entry>
<entry key="987">Currency fields cannot be used for grouping</entry>
<entry key="625">Date in the holiday list is invalid</entry>
<entry key="986">Currency value contains a currency code that is not allowed for this field</entry>
<entry key="624">User account locked out due to too many bad password attempts.</entry>
<entry key="985">No active Currency Code found on the Currency Code form.</entry>
<entry key="623">Authentication failed</entry>
<entry key="984">No Currency Code form exists</entry>
<entry key="622">Problem while preparing open write licensing -- open write licensing may be incomplete</entry>
<entry key="983">No common functional currency was found when currency constants were compared with functional currency data.</entry>
<entry key="621">Problem processing the license tag file -- license tag file ignored</entry>
<entry key="982">Bad currency value</entry>
<entry key="620">Two forms contain the same open license tag -- ignored for both forms</entry>
<entry key="981">Required currency code not specified</entry>
<entry key="980">Required currency value not specified</entry>
<entry key="619">Computed group list contains invalid information</entry>
<entry key="618">The syntax of the computed group qualification is incorrect.</entry>
<entry key="617">Computed group includes circular reference</entry>
<entry key="616">The specified Group ID is invalid for this group type.</entry>
<entry key="615">No such user exists</entry>
<entry key="614">License type can only be 0 (none), 1 (fixed), or 2 (floating).</entry>
<entry key="613">Group type can only be 1 (view) or 2 (change).</entry>
<entry key="612">No such user is registered with this server</entry>
<entry key="973">You don't have permission to the data on the results list.</entry>
<entry key="611">Dynamic group can not be in a computed group definition.</entry>
<entry key="972">Your query has no matches.</entry>
<entry key="610">Error while accessing server cache file (server.ar)</entry>
<entry key="971">Your query matched more than the configured maximum: {0}.\nThe maximum number of allowable matches are returned.</entry>
<entry key="970">There are {0} matches to your query request</entry>
<entry key="609">Invalid tag for Group or User operation</entry>
<entry key="608">A required value for the command line option is missing.</entry>
<entry key="969">--- AR Query Response ---</entry>
<entry key="607">An option required for the operation is missing.</entry>
<entry key="968">Invalid send to address. To:</entry>
<entry key="606">Invalid Allowed Client Types value: {0} \nExpecting integer values with delimiter ';'.</entry>
<entry key="967">"armail" could not log off from the mail system.</entry>
<entry key="605">One or more of the command line options is not appropriate for operation</entry>
<entry key="966">"armail" could not read a mail message from the mail system.</entry>
<entry key="604">Must specify the operation to be performed (-G or -U)</entry>
<entry key="965">The "armail" address specified is a duplicate within the mail system.</entry>
<entry key="603">Must specify one or both of the options -u and/or -g</entry>
<entry key="964">"armail" failed when trying to log in to the mail system.</entry>
<entry key="602">Cannot specify both -G and -U and cannot specify either more than once</entry>
<entry key="963">Your query request was accepted by the AR System</entry>
<entry key="601">Unrecognized command line option</entry>
<entry key="962">AR System Query Response</entry>
<entry key="600">Error while opening/reading from AR System directory file</entry>
<entry key="961">Your submission was accepted by the AR System.  ID for the new entry is</entry>
<entry key="960">AR System New Entry</entry>
<entry key="959">The server specified for this message is not a recognized server --\naccess was attempted but no server was found</entry>
<entry key="8206">Client has sent API call to a wrong RPC queue.</entry>
<entry key="958">The submitted mail message specified a server that does not match the required server</entry>
<entry key="8205">Port is busy --\ncheck with netstat to view ports in use</entry>
<entry key="957">The submitted mail message specified a form that does not match the required form</entry>
<entry key="8204">RPC control failed to set non-blocking I/O mode. Continuing in blocked I/O mode.</entry>
<entry key="956">Failure while accessing mail configuration file</entry>
<entry key="8203">The server's RPC version is not supported.</entry>
<entry key="955">Missing value for command line parameter</entry>
<entry key="8202">The RPC port specified is not one of the legal values (0, 1 - 65535)</entry>
<entry key="954">The proper format for this command is: armaild [-f filename] [-n number-of-intervals] [-d].</entry>
<entry key="8201">The RPC socket number specified is not one of the legal values (0, 390600, 390621 - 390634, 390636 - 390669, 390680 - 390694)</entry>
<entry key="953">The submitted mail message had a format that was not recognized</entry>
<entry key="952">The submitted mail message did not contain a body providing details for the new entry</entry>
<entry key="951">The submitted mail message did not contain a form name</entry>
<entry key="950">AR System error</entry>
<entry key="8552">Configuration-Name is missing from the configuration file.</entry>
<entry key="942">Can only copy server to file or file to server</entry>
<entry key="8551">This server information setting is no longer supported.</entry>
<entry key="941">DTYPES line missing from file</entry>
<entry key="8550">This api call is no longer supported.</entry>
<entry key="940">FLD_ID line missing from file</entry>
<entry key="9999">Should be either an aggregate field function or in the groupBy list</entry>
<entry key="9998">Aggregate field function not allowed in groupBy</entry>
<entry key="9997">Join query source has to be the only source in the list of query sources</entry>
<entry key="9996">Field function not valid</entry>
<entry key="9995">Invalid SQL clause included</entry>
<entry key="9994">Diary field or long char field not allowed in join criterion</entry>
<entry key="9993">Join qualifier not allowed for the first query source in the list</entry>
<entry key="9992">Dialog forms not allowed in a dynamic query.</entry>
<entry key="9991">Invalid join qualifier for this join form.</entry>
<entry key="9990">The ValueSetQuery property can only have one field.</entry>
<entry key="939">FIELDS line missing from file</entry>
<entry key="938">FORM line missing from file</entry>
<entry key="937">Form {0} does not exist on server {1}</entry>
<entry key="936">Unrecognized switch setting "{0}"</entry>
<entry key="935">Invalid switch setting "-id {0}"</entry>
<entry key="934">Multiple settings of the {0} switch</entry>
<entry key="933">ARMergeEntry returns an error.  Entry ID {0}.</entry>
<entry key="932">Found an invalid token of "{0}" in input file.  Bypassing.</entry>
<entry key="931">Internal buffer overflow for entry {0}, field {1}.  Bypassing.</entry>
<entry key="930">Usage: arcopy [source [dest [user [passwd]]]] [-id {new | old | fixup}]</entry>
<entry key="4198">Record {0} : Unrecognized tag in AR Export file: {1} (ARERR 4198)</entry>
<entry key="4196">AR Export file's Field ID string does not contain a number (ARERR 4196)</entry>
<entry key="4194">Cannot seek in import file (ARERR 4194): </entry>
<entry key="4192">Cannot open specified import file (ARERR 4192)</entry>
<entry key="9989">The list of the query fields must contain at least one regular field you have permission to</entry>
<entry key="4190">A field separator string is required (ARERR 4190)</entry>
<entry key="9988">Recursive query cannot be empty.</entry>
<entry key="9987">Field definition not valid</entry>
<entry key="9986">Join qualifier is specified but join source is not valid</entry>
<entry key="9985">The list of query sources can not be empty.</entry>
<entry key="9984">RegularQuery parameter cannot be empty.</entry>
<entry key="9983">Schema alias associated with the field is not valid</entry>
<entry key="9982">Wrong query type specified for an item in the query form list.</entry>
<entry key="9981">Wrong or missing join type</entry>
<entry key="9980">Wrong recursive schema specified in the Recursive Query</entry>
<entry key="8899">Overlay already exists</entry>
<entry key="8898">Cannot create overlay because the source and target object are not of the same type.</entry>
<entry key="8897">Delete this overlay group is not allowed.</entry>
<entry key="8896">Update this attribute of the overlay group is not allowed.</entry>
<entry key="8895">Overlay group includes circular reference</entry>
<entry key="8894">The struct admin does not have permission to operate in this overlay group.</entry>
<entry key="922">Form {0}:{1} contains no entries.  Bypassing.</entry>
<entry key="8893">Duplicate overlay group ID.</entry>
<entry key="921">A value is too long, it is being truncated</entry>
<entry key="8892">The granular overlay inherit mask is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="920">New line seen in quoted token</entry>
<entry key="8891">The granular overlay extend mask is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="8890">The granular overlay masks contain invalid or conflicting values.</entry>
<entry key="4188">The import field separator string is longer than the maximum allowed length. (ARERR 4188)</entry>
<entry key="4186">Import file name is longer than the maximum allowed length (ARERR 4186)</entry>
<entry key="4184">An import file name is required (ARERR 4184)</entry>
<entry key="4182">Specified import file has no data (ARERR 4182): </entry>
<entry key="9979">Can specify fields from only one schema in the Recursive Query fields list</entry>
<entry key="4180">Specified import file is empty (ARERR 4180): </entry>
<entry key="9977">Can not specify more than one Recursive Query </entry>
<entry key="9976">Wrong schema type specified for a query form list item in the Recursive Query.</entry>
<entry key="9975">There is no recursion qualifier specified in the Recursive Query</entry>
<entry key="9974">The Application_Interface fields can exist only on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="9973">The Application_Properties fields can exist only on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="9972">The fields reserved for respective System Log Forms can exist only on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="9971">Cannot find respective System Log Form.</entry>
<entry key="9970">The Application_Configuration_Registration fields can exist only on one form. Delete the duplicate.</entry>
<entry key="8889">This overlay object has been disabled</entry>
<entry key="8888">Overlay VUI changed field list is not of expected format or one of the fields in the list is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="8887">Data operations are not allowed in Full Mode.</entry>
<entry key="8886">Field display instance can be modified only when field is explicitly added to overlay VUI.</entry>
<entry key="8885">Base and overlay deployable application cannot have different export qualification or import option or merge field list for Data form.</entry>
<entry key="8884">To add custom form to an application, application needs to be either overlay or custom type.</entry>
<entry key="8883">Overlay of deployable application is required to enable audit/archive on overlay or custom form.</entry>
<entry key="8882">Only custom objects can be added/removed from custom or overlay deployable application.</entry>
<entry key="8881">A custom field with same field Id exists, conversion of custom to overlay is not allowed as field Id is beyond the reserved range.</entry>
<entry key="8880">Base object refers to custom or overlay object.</entry>
<entry key="4179">Cannot get the status of import file (ARERR 4179)</entry>
<entry key="4178">Specified import file is not a regular text file (ARERR 4178): </entry>
<entry key="4177">Specified import file is a directory (ARERR 4177): </entry>
<entry key="4176">Syntax error in the mapping string (ARERR 4176)</entry>
<entry key="4175">Specified import file does not exist (ARERR 4175)</entry>
<entry key="4174">Cannot parse import field titles in import file (ARERR 4174)</entry>
<entry key="4172">Record {0} : Cannot parse record in import file (ARERR 4172)</entry>
<entry key="4170">Bad Form Information UI Fields list. (ARERR 4170)</entry>
<entry key="9962">Only one form can contain the Tenant form fields</entry>
<entry key="9960">Recurrence of type Specific Dates has no dates.</entry>
<entry key="8879">Base object and custom object names are same. Conversion of custom to overlay is not allowed.</entry>
<entry key="8878">No permission to access object in overlay mode</entry>
<entry key="906">Copied {0} entries into {1}</entry>
<entry key="8877">No permission to access object in base mode</entry>
<entry key="905">Continuing....</entry>
<entry key="8876">The object is either custom or overlay object and converting it to custom or overlay in same overlay group is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="904">Processing form {0}:{1} containing {2} entries</entry>
<entry key="8875">Audit or archive form must be custom for the specified overlay form</entry>
<entry key="903">Processing form {0} from file {1}</entry>
<entry key="8874">Conversion of object from custom to base failed.</entry>
<entry key="902">Connecting to server {0}, form</entry>
<entry key="8873">Renaming of overlay object is not allowed</entry>
<entry key="901">Established {0} connection with {1}</entry>
<entry key="8510">Error creating a JMS subscriber</entry>
<entry key="8872">Unable to find the overlaid object</entry>
<entry key="900">Copying data from {0} to {1}</entry>
<entry key="8871">Field must be of custom type on given form.</entry>
<entry key="8870">To convert custom field to overlay, custom form name and the base form name must be the same.</entry>
<entry key="4168">Bad Fallback Mapping list (ARERR 4168)</entry>
<entry key="4166">Bad Mapping list (ARERR 4166)</entry>
<entry key="4164">Import fields' titles-list is invalid. (ARERR 4164)</entry>
<entry key="4162">Bad internal list (ARERR 4162)</entry>
<entry key="9959">The recurrence date is not valid for this month. Skipping to next recurrence. </entry>
<entry key="4160">Bad Mapping or Compound mapping within Compound mapping (ARERR 4160)</entry>
<entry key="9958">The date is out of range of the 1970 - 2038 allowed by the OS. </entry>
<entry key="9957">Day of the week selected is invalid. </entry>
<entry key="9956">Hours of day selected is invalid. </entry>
<entry key="9955">Day of Month selected is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="9954">Week of Month selected is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="9953">Month of year selected is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="9952">Type of recurrence requested is invalid. </entry>
<entry key="9951">The date entered is invalid or a bad date format. Please make sure the date format is in the ARServer's date format and separator.</entry>
<entry key="9950">The input provided for calculating the next recurrence is bad. </entry>
<entry key="8509">Error creating a JMS publisher</entry>
<entry key="8508">Error creating JMS connection factory</entry>
<entry key="8507">Error sending message through Java Messaging Service</entry>
<entry key="8869">To convert custom field to overlay, field Id of custom and base must be the same.</entry>
<entry key="8506">Error subscribing to Java Messaging Service topic - no such topic found</entry>
<entry key="8868">Field overlay and the associated view overlay must be in the same overlay group.</entry>
<entry key="8505">Error sending message through Java Messaging Service</entry>
<entry key="8867">Unable to find overlay for specified overlaid object</entry>
<entry key="8504">Error adding listener to Java Messaging Service </entry>
<entry key="8866">Audit/Archive form overlay and the associated base form overlay must be in the same overlay group.</entry>
<entry key="8503">Error receiving message from Java Messaging Service</entry>
<entry key="8865">Field/View overlay and the associated base form overlay must be in the same overlay group.</entry>
<entry key="8502">Error creating Java Messaging Service topic</entry>
<entry key="8864">Invalid value for overlay property</entry>
<entry key="8501">Error occurred while terminating Java Messaging Service</entry>
<entry key="8863">Before creating an overlay of a field or a form view, you must create an overlay of the object's associated form.</entry>
<entry key="8500">Error occurred while initializing Java Messaging Service</entry>
<entry key="8862">Names of custom objects must end in the suffix __c and can not exceed 80 characters.</entry>
<entry key="8861">Base and overlay object must be the same type.</entry>
<entry key="8860">The Group ID for Overlay and custom objects can only be 0 (does not belong to an overlay group) or 1 (belongs to the overlay group)</entry>
<entry key="4158">The mapping file has a syntax error (ARERR 4158)</entry>
<entry key="4156">The import option value is invalid (ARERR 4156)</entry>
<entry key="4155">Cannot read mapping file for specified mapping (ARERR 4153): </entry>
<entry key="4154">Cannot find specified mapping (ARERR 4153): </entry>
<entry key="4153">Cannot open mapping file for specified mapping (ARERR 4153): </entry>
<entry key="4152">No tokens for a Direct Mapping. (ARERR 4152)</entry>
<entry key="4150">Cannot set mapping list item (ARERR 4150)</entry>
<entry key="9940">Time-out during plug-in call--the request has been accepted by the plug-in server, but the plug-in has not yet responded</entry>
<entry key="8859">Invalid operation on overlay or overlaid object</entry>
<entry key="8858">__o is system reserved suffix and cannot be added manually.</entry>
<entry key="8857">Creating overlay is not supported for the type of object specified</entry>
<entry key="8856">An overlay and its corresponding overlaid object cannot belong to the same overlay group.</entry>
<entry key="8855">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted image</entry>
<entry key="8854">Child entries are not processed</entry>
<entry key="8853">Invalid locale info supplied</entry>
<entry key="8852">Server setting out of range</entry>
<entry key="8851">Setting BSM tag disallowed</entry>
<entry key="8850">A lock block must be exported entirely in xml or entirely in def format</entry>
<entry key="4148">Cannot add to mapping list (ARERR 4148)</entry>
<entry key="4146">Bad global variables.(ARERR 4146)</entry>
<entry key="4144">Bad parameters (ARERR 4144)</entry>
<entry key="4142">Cannot open the main import window. (ARERR 4142)</entry>
<entry key="4140">Cannot initialize the server API (ARERR 4140)</entry>
<entry key="9938">The field used for age qualification does not exist or is of not valid type. Only Date/Time fields are allowed in age qualification.</entry>
<entry key="9936">Audit option for Display Only fields can only be 'None'. Changing it to 'None'.</entry>
<entry key="9935">Fields in the range 5000 to 5999 are reserved for Audit use.</entry>
<entry key="9934">You cannot enable the audit on this form until you enable the audit on base forms.</entry>
<entry key="9933">You cannot disable the audit on this form until you disable the audit on dependent form.</entry>
<entry key="9932">Archive or Audit form not found. Archive or Audit will be disabled.</entry>
<entry key="9931">Qualification cannot contain EXTERNAL references.</entry>
<entry key="9930">Cannot import only Audit form. Either the Main form by itself or both Main and Audit can be imported.</entry>
<entry key="8849">Setting object lock information is disallowed at this time</entry>
<entry key="8848">Field deletion not allowed on a locked form</entry>
<entry key="8847">Field creation not allowed on a locked form</entry>
<entry key="8846">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted menu</entry>
<entry key="8845">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted escalation</entry>
<entry key="8844">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted filter</entry>
<entry key="8843">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted active link</entry>
<entry key="8842">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted container</entry>
<entry key="8841">Safeguard mismatch - potentially corrupted form</entry>
<entry key="8840">Attempt to modify a locked object - inappropriate changes are discarded</entry>
<entry key="4138">Cannot write to log file (ARERR 4138)</entry>
<entry key="4137">Log file {0} is not a regular text file (ARERR 4137)</entry>
<entry key="4499">User stopped import after {0} records were processed, of which {1} were imported (ARWARN 4499)</entry>
<entry key="4136">Import log file name is longer than the maximum allowed length (ARERR 4136)</entry>
<entry key="4135">Log file {0} is not a valid filename. (ARERR 4135)</entry>
<entry key="4134">A log file name is required (ARERR 4134)</entry>
<entry key="4132">Cannot get the status of or cannot open log file (ARERR 4132): </entry>
<entry key="9929">Field is missing from the Archive/Audit form.</entry>
<entry key="4130">"{0}" is not an import field name, id, or keyword (ARERR 4130)</entry>
<entry key="9928">The data types of the data fields in the Source and Archive/Audit form do not match.</entry>
<entry key="9927">The number of data fields in the main form should be less than or equal to the data fields in the Archive or Audit form.</entry>
<entry key="9926">The Archive or Audit form is already in use by another form.</entry>
<entry key="9925">There are incorrect number of reserved fields in the Archive or Audit form.</entry>
<entry key="9924">The same Log Key cannot be applied to more than one field in a schema.</entry>
<entry key="9923">Join form Audit cannot be enabled unless the base forms have audit enabled.</entry>
<entry key="9922">Audit not possible on Dialog or Audit forms.</entry>
<entry key="9921">Exporting locked object definitions are no longer supported.</entry>
<entry key="9920">Importing locked object definitions are no longer supported.</entry>
<entry key="8839">Cannot delete a locked object - must override to delete</entry>
<entry key="8838">No information is returned for the hidden locked object</entry>
<entry key="8837">End of file reached</entry>
<entry key="8836">Specified lock block cannot be found</entry>
<entry key="8835">Unable to load object lock information into cache</entry>
<entry key="8834">Lock information mismatch</entry>
<entry key="8833">Lock key cannot be changed, so the existing key will be kept</entry>
<entry key="8832">Unknown object lock level specified</entry>
<entry key="8831">Locking level cannot be decreased</entry>
<entry key="8830">Object cannot be locked</entry>
<entry key="4128">"{0}" is not a Form Field. (ARERR 4128)</entry>
<entry key="4126">A directory may be specified only if you specify a mapping (ARERR 4126)</entry>
<entry key="4124">The mapping name is longer than the maximum allowed length (ARERR 4124)</entry>
<entry key="4122">The -m option requires a mapping name (ARERR 4122)</entry>
<entry key="4120">Two mappings have been specified on the command line. Only one mapping is allowed. (ARERR 4120)</entry>
<entry key="9913">The form definition VUI count does not match the number of VUIs in the database.</entry>
<entry key="9912">The form definition field count does not match the number of fields in the database.</entry>
<entry key="9911">Admin operations are suspended because the number of open caches is at the configured limit.</entry>
<entry key="9910">Admin operations are suspended because the number of open caches is at the configured limit.</entry>
<entry key="8821">Computed Group Cannot have Overlay. Setting Overlay Group to Null.</entry>
<entry key="8820">Create Overlay is not supported for Status History Field.</entry>
<entry key="4118">Cannot login to any AR Server (ARERR 4118)</entry>
<entry key="4116">Cannot get children widgets, or widget not a child (ARERR 4116)</entry>
<entry key="4114">No saved mappings specified in batch mode (ARERR 4114)</entry>
<entry key="4112">No mapping selected to delete. (ARERR 4112)</entry>
<entry key="4110">The record starting at the specified offset cannot be read. (ARERR 4110)</entry>
<entry key="9908">Illegal operation for placeholder schema</entry>
<entry key="9907">Illegal command line parameter</entry>
<entry key="9906">Size of memory allocation for result exceeded configured limit on the server</entry>
<entry key="9905">Internal API call failed</entry>
<entry key="9902">External Logging Not Handled</entry>
<entry key="9901">External Logging Error</entry>
<entry key="9900">External Logging Note</entry>
<entry key="8819">Application owner does not match what's defined in the schema for schema.</entry>
<entry key="8818">The container is not supported by the server</entry>
<entry key="3380">The DN Entry for this request has timed out. Re-enter Search request</entry>
<entry key="8817">The value of the external reference has an invalid format</entry>
<entry key="8816">Illegal reference type</entry>
<entry key="2299">You have entered too many parameters in a function assignment</entry>
<entry key="8815">Missing or invalid container definition file</entry>
<entry key="2298">Value specified for selection not one of defined values for this field</entry>
<entry key="8814">No container ID for the container</entry>
<entry key="2297">Unknown field reference</entry>
<entry key="8813">Error encountered with the flat file database container file (contain.ar)</entry>
<entry key="2296">Expected a closing parenthesis at this point</entry>
<entry key="8812">Container cannot be owned by this type of object</entry>
<entry key="2295">Too many nested levels of parenthesis in command</entry>
<entry key="8811">No name was specified for the owning object</entry>
<entry key="2294">Expected a field or value at this point</entry>
<entry key="8810">The specified container already exists</entry>
<entry key="2293">Expected a relational operation at this point</entry>
<entry key="2292">Expected a conditional operation at this point</entry>
<entry key="2291">Unexpected character</entry>
<entry key="4108">The message broadcast was stopped. (ARERR 4108)</entry>
<entry key="2290">Missing close quote on a character string/name</entry>
<entry key="4106">\n     Copying remaining records of {0} to log file</entry>
<entry key="4105">The import operation was terminated by user. (ARERR 4105)</entry>
<entry key="4104">Import completed with errors:\n     {0} records were imported; {1} records were not (ARERR 4104)</entry>
<entry key="4102">Invalid AR Export format file:\n{0} (ARERR 4102)</entry>
<entry key="4100">{0}\nUsage: {1} [-x server] [-m mapping-name] [-d startup-directory] [-b]</entry>
<entry key="3379">To create objects, the distinguished name must have a value.</entry>
<entry key="3378">At least one field on the form must reference the Distinguished Name attribute</entry>
<entry key="3377">The LDAP operation has failed</entry>
<entry key="3376">The specified LDAP URL is not formatted correctly</entry>
<entry key="3375">Cannot connect to the directory service</entry>
<entry key="8809">Illegal container type</entry>
<entry key="8808">The specified flat file database file is not a valid container file</entry>
<entry key="8807">Unable to open the specified container</entry>
<entry key="8806">The specified container is missing</entry>
<entry key="2289">No data to paste</entry>
<entry key="8805">You do not have access to the specified container</entry>
<entry key="2288">You must select at least one operation</entry>
<entry key="8804">The specified container does not exist</entry>
<entry key="2287">You must select a form</entry>
<entry key="8803">The description of the specified reference is empty</entry>
<entry key="2286">The message number is invalid</entry>
<entry key="8802">The label of the specified reference is empty</entry>
<entry key="2285">Enter a filter name</entry>
<entry key="8801">The value of the specified reference is empty</entry>
<entry key="2284">No data entered at previous menu level</entry>
<entry key="8800">The specified container owner name is incorrect</entry>
<entry key="2283">You must enter a label before selecting Insert or Modify</entry>
<entry key="2282">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2281">No data entered at selected menu level</entry>
<entry key="2280">Only fields created since last Apply can be deleted</entry>
<entry key="3005">AR System Server is now available</entry>
<entry key="3004">AR System Server is not currently available -- will retry connection</entry>
<entry key="3003">Pending distributed operation canceled due to error</entry>
<entry key="3002">Entry pending transfer or update has been pending for longer than the specified retry timeout</entry>
<entry key="3001">AR System Distributed Server terminated -- fatal error encountered</entry>
<entry key="3000">If signal is 15: "AR System Distributed Server terminated by user or accidentally."</entry>
<entry key="2279">Problem deleting selected item from list during cut operation</entry>
<entry key="2278">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2277">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2276">You cannot delete an object that you are currently editing</entry>
<entry key="2275">Cannot get custom view list</entry>
<entry key="2274">Cannot find selected item in UIFieldStruct list</entry>
<entry key="2273">Cannot locate field list in key data</entry>
<entry key="2272">Cannot create new item</entry>
<entry key="2271">Cannot destroy old item</entry>
<entry key="2270">Bad default</entry>
<entry key="3357">Required report field is missing</entry>
<entry key="3356">Invalid report definition encountered</entry>
<entry key="3355">Illegal field encountered in the qualifier</entry>
<entry key="3354">Illegal field encountered in the sort list</entry>
<entry key="3353">Illegal field encountered in the field list</entry>
<entry key="3352">Unable to create temporary file for report definition file </entry>
<entry key="3351">Unable to get temporary file name for report definition file</entry>
<entry key="3350">Unable to locate Report form</entry>
<entry key="2269">Select an item</entry>
<entry key="2268">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2267">The forked process failed to execute</entry>
<entry key="2266">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2265">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2264">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2263">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2262">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2261">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2260">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="299">Too many levels in filter processing</entry>
<entry key="298">Too many filters processed during this operation</entry>
<entry key="297">Admin released license too recently </entry>
<entry key="296">Invalid support file type</entry>
<entry key="295">File pointer is NULL or invalid file pointer.</entry>
<entry key="3342">Unable to write to arsignal daemon.</entry>
<entry key="294">Requested number of entries exceeds maximum allowed.</entry>
<entry key="3341">Not enough memory to to create arsignald start up info.</entry>
<entry key="293">Expected column data missing from multiple entries</entry>
<entry key="3340">Unable to start the arsignald process.</entry>
<entry key="292">Invalid item list for entry existence</entry>
<entry key="291">Message text is empty or too long</entry>
<entry key="2259">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="290">Cannot access the join form with this version of the client.</entry>
<entry key="2258">Create of user command failed -- duplicate name?</entry>
<entry key="2257">Enter a command string to execute</entry>
<entry key="2256">Duplicate name for a user command</entry>
<entry key="2255">Enter a command name</entry>
<entry key="2254">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2253">Unable to execute your selected command</entry>
<entry key="2252">Cannot locate your selected command</entry>
<entry key="2251">Error creating the custom user command menu</entry>
<entry key="2250">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="3338">Some operations owned by the current server in the server group are not configured for failover to another server</entry>
<entry key="3337">Server group management action postponed due to a Development cache mode write lock on the cache</entry>
<entry key="289">Nested outer join is not supported by Sybase /SQL database.</entry>
<entry key="3336">Duplicate server group ranking value encountered in the ranking form -- ordering cannot be guaranteed</entry>
<entry key="288">The requested operation is not supported on the server</entry>
<entry key="3335">The Check Interval setting change will only take effect after all servers in the group are restarted.</entry>
<entry key="287">Status field must be created before status history field can be created</entry>
<entry key="3334">Invalid or missing server group license entry. Contact your AR System administrator.</entry>
<entry key="286">Display only fields cannot be included in a query to the database</entry>
<entry key="3333">Invalid or missing server group operation definition. Contact your AR System administrator.</entry>
<entry key="285">A field referenced in the qualification is not a data field</entry>
<entry key="3332">The change of this setting will only take effect after AR System server restart.</entry>
<entry key="284">Escalation does not have an action defined</entry>
<entry key="3331">A floating license with a different server group tag cannot be used on this server group. This floating license is ignored.</entry>
<entry key="283">The specified data type is not supported.</entry>
<entry key="3330">A floating license with server group tag cannot be used on a stand-alone server. This floating license is ignored.</entry>
<entry key="282">A default view for this form already exists.</entry>
<entry key="281">Multiple links can not be mapped to the same button.</entry>
<entry key="2249">Cannot build the user command menu</entry>
<entry key="280">AR System entry calls to join forms are not supported in a Flat File database</entry>
<entry key="2248">Cannot build the form menu</entry>
<entry key="2247">Cannot build the server menu</entry>
<entry key="2246">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2245">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2244">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2243">Cannot open the specified file</entry>
<entry key="2242">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2241">No selection made -- one is required</entry>
<entry key="2240">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="3329">A floating license without server group tag cannot be used in a server group. This floating license is ignored.</entry>
<entry key="3328">Unable to launch an agent process to communicate with an external program.</entry>
<entry key="3327">Check interval cannot be less than 30 seconds.  A 30-second value is set by the system.</entry>
<entry key="279">Selection Value ID too large.</entry>
<entry key="3326">Unable to find a server group entry for this server</entry>
<entry key="278">This field is used in a join form qualification and with No Delete flag set.</entry>
<entry key="3325">Unable to send a server group related signal to another server.</entry>
<entry key="277">The field is referenced by a join form as a base field with No Delete flag set.</entry>
<entry key="3324">This configuration setting is not allowed when the server is a member of a server group</entry>
<entry key="276">This form can not be deleted because it is referenced by a join form as a base form with "No Delete" flag set.</entry>
<entry key="3323">Creation of the server group operation ranking form failed.</entry>
<entry key="275">Index not allowed on join form.</entry>
<entry key="3322">Unrecognized server group operation encountered in the ranking form</entry>
<entry key="274">After a form (base, join, or view) is created, you cannot change the form type.</entry>
<entry key="3321">No server group operation ranking form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="273">Invalid field mapping type</entry>
<entry key="3320">The reserved server group fields can only exist on one form-- delete duplicates on other forms to continue.</entry>
<entry key="272">The table name identified in the view form definition does not exist.</entry>
<entry key="271">A form field is tied to an invalid index.</entry>
<entry key="2239">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="270">Field mapping is empty.</entry>
<entry key="2238">Not Applicable</entry>
<entry key="2237">Not Applicable for MenuBar/Separator</entry>
<entry key="2236">Problem querying servers</entry>
<entry key="2235">Problem reading server directory</entry>
<entry key="2234">Enter a user name</entry>
<entry key="2233">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2232">Enter a form name</entry>
<entry key="2231">X and/or Y coordinates are out of range</entry>
<entry key="2230">Update of custom operation failed -- duplicate name?</entry>
<entry key="3319">Unable to connect with alert client.</entry>
<entry key="3318">Attempt to communicate with alert client failed because the required port is in use by another process.</entry>
<entry key="3317">Invalid alert message format</entry>
<entry key="269">Invalid form type in join or view form definition.</entry>
<entry key="3316">Failed to load the alert cleanup escalation</entry>
<entry key="268">Invalid view form definition</entry>
<entry key="3315">Attempt to communicate with alert client timed out.</entry>
<entry key="267">Invalid join form qualification</entry>
<entry key="3314">Failed to connect with alert client.</entry>
<entry key="266">Invalid join member form name</entry>
<entry key="265">Join or View form definition is empty.</entry>
<entry key="264">Server name for a character menu is empty or too long</entry>
<entry key="263">Unrecognized save login code</entry>
<entry key="262">Field having length over 255 bytes (including diary fields, unlimited length character fields, and the Status History field) cannot be used as fields to group by</entry>
<entry key="261">SQL command is empty.</entry>
<entry key="2229">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="260">Unrecognized multiple match action.</entry>
<entry key="2228">Cannot open configuration file</entry>
<entry key="2227">Export complete for selected range</entry>
<entry key="2226">Export Range</entry>
<entry key="2225">Export Error</entry>
<entry key="2224">Export complete</entry>
<entry key="2223">Exporting . . .</entry>
<entry key="2222">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2221">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2220">Button field is missing an Active Link assignment.</entry>
<entry key="259">Unrecognized no match action.</entry>
<entry key="258">The RPC socket number for the Distributed Server process is not one of the legal values (390600, 390621 - 390634, 390636 - 390669, 390680 - 390694)</entry>
<entry key="257">A display tag to identify the view is not unique.</entry>
<entry key="256">Unrecognized server statistics tag</entry>
<entry key="3303">Must be AR_NOTIFIER user to perform this operation</entry>
<entry key="255">Unrecognized submitter mode</entry>
<entry key="3302">Problem encountered during creation of the Alert Events form</entry>
<entry key="254">Subject line is longer than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="3301">The reserved alert event fields exist on multiple forms. They are only allowed to exist on one form.</entry>
<entry key="253">One or more groups in the list of groups granted Subadministrator access to a form does not exist.</entry>
<entry key="3300">No Alert Events form could be found on the server</entry>
<entry key="252">One or more groups in the list of groups for the Subadministrator is not a group defined on this system.</entry>
<entry key="251">Invalid value for enabling or disabling a filter/active link/escalation</entry>
<entry key="2219">Form definition problem: invalid field specification</entry>
<entry key="250">Invalid minute format.</entry>
<entry key="2218">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2217">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2216">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2215">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2214">Cannot open export file</entry>
<entry key="2213">No text has been selected for your query parameter</entry>
<entry key="2212">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2211">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2210">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="4740">No alternate metadata table names table.</entry>
<entry key="249">Invalid hour format.</entry>
<entry key="248">Invalid day selection</entry>
<entry key="247">Invalid interval time</entry>
<entry key="246">Invalid day format </entry>
<entry key="244">The path to the program field of the DDE active link action is missing or is too large.</entry>
<entry key="243">DDE definition is empty</entry>
<entry key="242">The specified field, value, or arithmetic operation type is not supported outside of a filter qualification.</entry>
<entry key="241">Fields that have lengths over 255 bytes (including diary fields,\nunlimited length character fields, and the Status History field) \ncannot be specified as fields in the list returned by the Get List function.</entry>
<entry key="2209">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="240">Fields that have lengths over 255 bytes (including diary fields,\nunlimited length character fields, and the Status History field) cannot be specified as sort fields.</entry>
<entry key="2208">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2207">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2206">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2205">Unrecognized field type</entry>
<entry key="2204">Only selection type can use choice box</entry>
<entry key="2203">Only selection type can use radio buttons</entry>
<entry key="2202">Only integer type can use numeric text type</entry>
<entry key="2201">NOT USED</entry>
<entry key="2200">Cannot allocate memory</entry>
<entry key="4737">Error renaming table or column in ArChgId Restore table.</entry>
<entry key="4736">Error retrieving/inserting entry in ArChgId Restore table.</entry>
<entry key="4735">Error creating or dropping ArChgId Restore table in DB.</entry>
<entry key="4734">Warning, unsupported form type.</entry>
<entry key="4733">Error processing alternate data form entry.</entry>
<entry key="4732">Error during restore or rollback of alternate data tables in DB.</entry>
<entry key="4731">Error creating alternate data tables in DB.</entry>
<entry key="4730">Error creating or dropping alt data form table in DB.</entry>
<entry key="239">Invalid DDE action.</entry>
<entry key="238">Value for DDE item is larger than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="237">Value specified for DDE service name or topic is missing or larger than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="236">license timeout cannot be less than 1 hour.</entry>
<entry key="598">API and SQL operation did not complete prior to the client timeout</entry>
<entry key="235">Invalid user list type.</entry>
<entry key="597">API operation did not complete prior to the client timeout</entry>
<entry key="234">Value specified for the filter/escalation 'set fields' process timeout exceeds the range of 1 to 60 seconds.</entry>
<entry key="596">API operation elapsed time has exceeded the configured threshold</entry>
<entry key="233">Invalid parameter setting in function definition.</entry>
<entry key="595">SQL operation elapsed time has exceeded the configured threshold</entry>
<entry key="232">Incompatible value types in a value list.</entry>
<entry key="231">Parameter list for a function is empty</entry>
<entry key="230">The specified function code is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="592">SQL database is now available</entry>
<entry key="591">SQL database is still not available -- continuing to attempt connection</entry>
<entry key="590">SQL database is not available -- will retry connection</entry>
<entry key="4726">Error creating/deleting entry in deferred delete table.</entry>
<entry key="4725">Error creating deferred delete table.</entry>
<entry key="1102">Additional errors were truncated</entry>
<entry key="1101">Error occurred during execution of active link {0} -- action {1}</entry>
<entry key="4721">Error dropping metadata table.</entry>
<entry key="1100">The entry was successfully created with ID = {0}</entry>
<entry key="4720">Error copying metadata table.</entry>
<entry key="229">Function to be performed is not defined.</entry>
<entry key="228">Unrecognized value for set access option characteristic</entry>
<entry key="227">Unrecognized value for set focus characteristic</entry>
<entry key="226">Type of field, value, or arithmetic operation is not supported on the GetListEntry operation</entry>
<entry key="225">Set fields actions in a filter/escalation that reference entries in other forms can only reference forms on the same server.</entry>
<entry key="224">Cannot index a diary field, an unlimited length field, or a field with a maximum length over 255 bytes</entry>
<entry key="223">The action tag for multiple match is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="222">Query contains an error.</entry>
<entry key="221">Query value is empty.</entry>
<entry key="220">Local variable number is out of range (must be 0 to 10)</entry>
<entry key="4711">Import options conflict.</entry>
<entry key="4710">This form is read only during install.</entry>
<entry key="1451">Failure trying to run a process to load a field value</entry>
<entry key="1450">Failure during fork operation</entry>
<entry key="219">Incorrect Server information data type.</entry>
<entry key="218">Server information associated with this tag cannot be viewed.</entry>
<entry key="217">Update to Server information associated with this tag is not allowed.</entry>
<entry key="216">ARServerInfoList is empty.</entry>
<entry key="215">The total length of the results list is greater than the maximum allowed.</entry>
<entry key="214">One of the items in the display list of field definitions is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="213">Qualifier parameter is empty -- must be a pointer to memory.</entry>
<entry key="212">Display list is empty</entry>
<entry key="211">Incorrect number of allowed fields are specified in a single index.</entry>
<entry key="210">Total length of all fields in an index is greater than the maximum length allowed.</entry>
<entry key="570">Incorrect format in the SQL command</entry>
<entry key="4709">This operation can only be done by the install host.</entry>
<entry key="4708">Admin operations restricted to installer or special install user.</entry>
<entry key="4707">This operation can only be done during upgrade mode InProcess.</entry>
<entry key="4706">Admin operations restricted due to installation.</entry>
<entry key="4705">Must be in production cache mode.</entry>
<entry key="4704">Unrecognized zero downtime installer signal.</entry>
<entry key="4703">Can't rollback now.</entry>
<entry key="4702">Can't set to new mode from current mode.</entry>
<entry key="4701">Invalid upgrade admin state requested.</entry>
<entry key="4700">Invalid upgrade mode requested.</entry>
<entry key="209">Filename for a character menu is empty, or too long.</entry>
<entry key="208">Unrecognized character menu file location</entry>
<entry key="207">Unrecognized character menu refresh code</entry>
<entry key="569">The number of database records affected by a SQL statement was not available from the database</entry>
<entry key="206">Unrecognized character menu type</entry>
<entry key="567">Failed to connect to database after multiple attempts</entry>
<entry key="204">Notify priority is out of range (0 to 10)</entry>
<entry key="566">Requested record is locked by another user, please retry.</entry>
<entry key="203">Value list is empty</entry>
<entry key="565">The requested value is beyond the number of values returned.</entry>
<entry key="202">The name specified for the user to be notified is too long.</entry>
<entry key="564">Field references on the right side of the LIKE operation are not supported by SQL database.</entry>
<entry key="201">Unrecognized or misused tag for field/value definition</entry>
<entry key="563">'%' cannot used to search for entries in SQL database.</entry>
<entry key="200">Macro value string is longer than the maximum allowed length</entry>
<entry key="562">Help text or change diary definition is missing.</entry>
<entry key="561">The underlying database does not support qualifications on fields \nwith a length over 4000 bytes for Oracle or 255 bytes for all other databases</entry>
<entry key="560">Multiple actions have the same internal index (likely data corruption)</entry>
<entry key="559">Character string exceeds maximum size allowed</entry>
<entry key="558">Form or field definition is missing.</entry>
<entry key="557">More data was found in the database than was expected.</entry>
<entry key="556">Missing data in the SQL database</entry>
<entry key="555">One or more selection values are missing from the data dictionary in the database.</entry>
<entry key="554">The Control record for the data dictionary in the database is missing.</entry>
<entry key="553">Operation requested is too large for a single SQL command</entry>
<entry key="552">The SQL database operation failed.</entry>
<entry key="551">Unable to connect to the SQL database.</entry>
<entry key="550">Unable to connect to the SQL database.\nPlease ensure the SQL database is running or contact the Database Administrator for help.</entry>
<entry key="1416">Cannot make backup view</entry>
<entry key="1415">Cannot restore previous view</entry>
<entry key="1414">Cannot reset user view</entry>
<entry key="1413">Cannot write to the default file</entry>
<entry key="1412">Cannot write to the view file</entry>
<entry key="1411">Cannot write to the definition file</entry>
<entry key="899">Can not begin transaction because a transaction is already open.</entry>
<entry key="898">Transaction handle supplied is invalid.</entry>
<entry key="897">Maximum number of client transactions already in use.</entry>
<entry key="896">Overlay association type can not be changed.</entry>
<entry key="895">Sort Item must exist in Selection list if distinct is specified</entry>
<entry key="894">WhenThen list for case is empty</entry>
<entry key="893">Case to be performed is not defined.</entry>
<entry key="892">Functions or Case in qualification are not supported for this api</entry>
<entry key="891">ARGetListValueFromEntries is not supported for form</entry>
<entry key="890">ARGetListValueFromEntries is not supported for Vendor form and Join form with vendor base forms</entry>
<entry key="1409">Cannot write to the specified file</entry>
<entry key="1408">Cannot read from the specified file</entry>
<entry key="1407">Cannot open a temporary file</entry>
<entry key="1406">Cannot open the specified file</entry>
<entry key="1405">Cannot open configuration file</entry>
<entry key="1404">Cannot open default file</entry>
<entry key="1402">Cannot open definition file</entry>
<entry key="1401">Cannot open view file</entry>
<entry key="526">Upload is allowed with warning</entry>
<entry key="525">File is not allowed to be uploaded.</entry>
<entry key="524">This operation encountered an error and the transaction has been rolled back.</entry>
<entry key="885">No image type specified</entry>
<entry key="523">Error encountered with the flat file database alert time file (alerttim.ar)</entry>
<entry key="884">No image specified</entry>
<entry key="522">Error encountered with the flat file database alert user file (alertusr.ar)</entry>
<entry key="883">Duplicate image name</entry>
<entry key="521">Error encountered with the flat file database attachment BLOB file index</entry>
<entry key="882">The specified image could not be found</entry>
<entry key="520">Error encountered with the flat file database attachment BLOB file</entry>
<entry key="881">Image definition is missing.</entry>
<entry key="518">Error encountered with the flat file database support detail file</entry>
<entry key="517">Error encountered with the flat file database support file file (supfile.ar)</entry>
<entry key="878">Cannot delete a field designated as Weighted relevancy field</entry>
<entry key="516">Error encountered with the flat file database escalation file (escl.ar)</entry>
<entry key="877">Weighted relevancy field must have public permission</entry>
<entry key="515">Error encountered with the flat file database character menu file (charmenu.ar)</entry>
<entry key="876">Cannot un-index a field which is designated as a weighted relevancy field</entry>
<entry key="514">Contents of the Status-History field in the flat file database are missing or invalid</entry>
<entry key="875">FTS Service could not complete the requested operation.</entry>
<entry key="513">Flat file database data record overflow</entry>
<entry key="874">A required parameter is null or invalid</entry>
<entry key="512">Error encountered with the flat file database active link file (actlink.ar)</entry>
<entry key="873">Invalid debug option specified</entry>
<entry key="511">Error encountered with the flat file database group cache file (group.ar)</entry>
<entry key="872">Form name specified invalid</entry>
<entry key="510">Error encountered with the flat file database user cache file (user.ar)</entry>
<entry key="871">Form ID already specified</entry>
<entry key="870">Form name already specified</entry>
<entry key="509">Error encountered with the flat file database administrator command file (adminext.ar)</entry>
<entry key="508">Error encountered with the flat file database filter file (filter.ar)</entry>
<entry key="869">Too many arguments specified for the retry argument.</entry>
<entry key="507">Error encountered with the flat file database data file (xxx.db)</entry>
<entry key="868">Too many arguments specified for the optimize argument.</entry>
<entry key="506">Error encountered with the flat file database definition file (xxx.def)</entry>
<entry key="867">A form ID or name, a field ID, and a Request ID are all required for this operation. One or more of these values is missing.</entry>
<entry key="505">Error encountered with the flat file database form file (schema.ar)</entry>
<entry key="866">Another instance of the full text indexer process is already running.</entry>
<entry key="504">Missing or invalid form definition file</entry>
<entry key="865">Full text indexer process terminated by user or a system error.</entry>
<entry key="503">Failure during write to flat file database data file</entry>
<entry key="864">Invalid action for full text indexer process</entry>
<entry key="502">Flat file database format error</entry>
<entry key="863">Too many arguments for the full text indexer process</entry>
<entry key="501">The specified flat file database file is not a valid data file</entry>
<entry key="862">Too few arguments for the full text indexer process</entry>
<entry key="500">Failure while trying to open the flat file database data file (check Server-directory setting)</entry>
<entry key="861">Failed to delete unneeded entries while reindexing the pending list.</entry>
<entry key="860">Unable to add note about the field updated due to the failure to truncate the file holding the indexing pending list.</entry>
<entry key="859">Unable to add note about the field updated due to the failure of locating the record associated with the updated field.</entry>
<entry key="858">Unable to add note about the field updated due to the failure of writing to the pending list indexing file.</entry>
<entry key="857">Unable to add note about the field updated due to the failure of opening the pending list indexing file.</entry>
<entry key="856">Pending list lock file does not exist</entry>
<entry key="855">Failed to lock arservftd process, it is held by another process.</entry>
<entry key="851">Unable to read from the pipe</entry>
<entry key="850">Unable to open the pipe</entry>
<entry key="849">Unable to create the pipe</entry>
<entry key="848">Unable to start any servers -- TC server will be shut down</entry>
<entry key="847">A failure occurred while the system tried to wait for a status change.</entry>
<entry key="846">Exception occurred while handling previous exception</entry>
<entry key="845">Unable to start this server 4 tries within 30 seconds - abandoning attempt.</entry>
<entry key="844">Unable to launch the child process.</entry>
<entry key="843">Unable to launch the child process.</entry>
<entry key="842">Not enough memory to process the call from the client.</entry>
<entry key="841">Another copy of the TC server is already running</entry>
<entry key="840">Error while opening the AR System TC server lock file</entry>
<entry key="8798">AR Plugin Server Startup Error - Invalid Plugin Port</entry>
<entry key="8797">Error encountered while encoding bytes to string</entry>
<entry key="8796">Plugin Delete Instance Error</entry>
<entry key="8795">Plugin Create Instance Error</entry>
<entry key="8794">Plugin Termination Error</entry>
<entry key="8793">AR Plugin Server Startup Error</entry>
<entry key="8792">Exception occured while loading the native plugin host library</entry>
<entry key="8791">AR System Plugin Server Version 7.1.0. Started up.</entry>
<entry key="8790">Unknown system error</entry>
<entry key="9875">Feature Not Supported</entry>
<entry key="9874">Invalid Breakpoint ID.</entry>
<entry key="9873">Command not valid at this time.</entry>
<entry key="9872">Error in field value list (bad ID or datatype)</entry>
<entry key="9871">Execution terminated by workflow debugger</entry>
<entry key="9870">Escalations must be disabled</entry>
<entry key="8789">Error encountered while encoding string to bytes</entry>
<entry key="8788">Error fetching public key.</entry>
<entry key="8787">Error fetching private key.</entry>
<entry key="8786">Error while setting up public/private key pair.</entry>
<entry key="8785">Data decryption error encountered</entry>
<entry key="8784">Data encryption error encountered</entry>
<entry key="8783">Unknown host. Usage: java ARPluginServerMain -x hostname -t portnum -i workingfolder</entry>
<entry key="8782">Invalid port number. Usage: java ARPluginServerMain -x hostname -t portnum -i workingfolder</entry>
<entry key="8781">Invalid Command line arguments. Usage: java ARPluginServerMain -x hostname -t portnum -i workingfolder</entry>
<entry key="8780">Duplicate User</entry>
<entry key="9864">The Application or the Form cannot be made licensable. Only deployable applications\n can be made licensable. Also, Forms have to belong to deployable applications to be made licensable.</entry>
<entry key="9863">No license property can be set while creating a form.</entry>
<entry key="9862">No free application user floating write license are available. \nCurrently accessing the application form in read-only mode. \nLicense will upgrade when one is available.</entry>
<entry key="9861">The form is missing application licensing information</entry>
<entry key="9860">The application license format is not valid</entry>
<entry key="804">AR System TC server restarting</entry>
<entry key="803">AR System server terminated unexpectedly -- restarting</entry>
<entry key="802">AR System server terminated unexpectedly -- restarting</entry>
<entry key="801">AR System TC server terminated -- fatal error encountered</entry>
<entry key="8410">The entire operation failed</entry>
<entry key="800">AR System TC server terminated by the server.</entry>
<entry key="8771">Duplicate name detected for plugin. Skipping duplicate entry</entry>
<entry key="8770">The RPC socket number for plug-in loopback is not one of the legal values (390621 - 390634, 390636 - 390669, 390680 - 390694)</entry>
<entry key="9859">The license information provided for this form does not match that in owning application</entry>
<entry key="9858">The application is not licensed </entry>
<entry key="9857">Application or Form already Licensable. Cannot modify or unlicense the Application or Form.</entry>
<entry key="9856">There is no such application user fixed license on the system: </entry>
<entry key="9855">The following write application token has become available and has been allocated to you --\naccess has been upgraded to write access</entry>
<entry key="9854">The following application fixed licenses have been granted:</entry>
<entry key="9853">The following application fixed licenses have been returned to the system:</entry>
<entry key="9852">An Application fixed license of this type has been assigned to more users than the number of valid licenses you have: </entry>
<entry key="9851">No additional application fixed license for this type of license is available: </entry>
<entry key="9850">You do not have application write license</entry>
<entry key="8409">Data type of existing and new field is different</entry>
<entry key="8408">Join and base field types must be the same</entry>
<entry key="8407">Permission denied because the user is not the task owner</entry>
<entry key="8769">Invalid configuration for a plugin. One of the required values was not provided</entry>
<entry key="8406">Cannot delete open task</entry>
<entry key="8768">Could not load/Save the plugin server configuration file</entry>
<entry key="1">Message not in catalog -- message number = </entry>
<entry key="8405">Checkpoint creation failed</entry>
<entry key="8767">Error while loading Java wrapper for native plugin</entry>
<entry key="8404">Task creation failed</entry>
<entry key="8766">Error encountered while invoking a Native plugin host call:  </entry>
<entry key="8403">Duplicate checkpoint</entry>
<entry key="8765">Error while initializing the JNI type manager for native plugins</entry>
<entry key="8402">Checkpoint not found</entry>
<entry key="8764">Error while loading the native plugin hosting library arpluginjni</entry>
<entry key="8401">Duplicate task</entry>
<entry key="8763">The specified plug-in failed to set properties</entry>
<entry key="8400">Task not found</entry>
<entry key="8762">The specified plug-in failed to initialize properly.  Contact your AR System Administrator for assistance.</entry>
<entry key="8761">An invalid password has been used for access to the plug-in server.  Contact your AR System Administrator for assistance.</entry>
<entry key="8760">Cannot establish a network connection to the AR System Plug-In server</entry>
<entry key="8759">The plug-in does not implement ARPluginIdentify().  The plug-in will not load.</entry>
<entry key="8758">The plug-in name is empty, contains invalid characters, or is a reserved name.  The plug-in will not load.</entry>
<entry key="8756">An error has occurred while loading a plug-in.</entry>
<entry key="8755">The specified plug-in does not exist.</entry>
<entry key="8754">Retrieving attachment data is not supported for this form.</entry>
<entry key="8753">Error in plugin</entry>
<entry key="8752">Delete entry operations are not supported for this form.</entry>
<entry key="8751">Set entry operations are not supported for this form.</entry>
<entry key="8750">Create entry operations are not supported for this form.</entry>
</properties>
